<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<sentences>
	<sentence id="645">
		<text>I really thought this movie was a smashing one, given the fact that it created a hype in Holland and the reviews really praised the film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1023">
		<text>the drama was a little cheezy but overall the film was worthwhile.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="drama" polarity="negative" from="4" to="9"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="248">
		<text>Still feels like yesterday when I first saw this come out</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="52">
		<text>I guess if you get kicks out of people whose lives are completely the dumps then watch this movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="737">
		<text>I would have tweaked little things here and there but overall this film can only be described as Phenomenal.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="928">
		<text>Story line was on the spot.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Story line" polarity="positive" from="0" to="10"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="238">
		<text>I love the creativity of the entire plot and the characters.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="positive" from="36" to="40"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="532">
		<text>To see this rated better than &quot;One flew over cuckoos nest&quot; that shows way better cruelty saddens me.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="280">
		<text>If you knows at least how the Bow works....</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="434">
		<text>Mind-blowing movies I like it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1003">
		<text>Russel Crowe does a fantastic job as Maximus and Pheonix is great as Commodus.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Russel Crowe" polarity="positive" from="0" to="12"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Pheonix" polarity="positive" from="49" to="56"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="790">
		<text>i must say..you must watch this one.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="84">
		<text>I'd rather see the Matrix.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="the Matrix" polarity="positive" from="15" to="25"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="725">
		<text>Words can't even describe how good this movie is I love it I could watch it thousands time and probably will</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="497">
		<text>If Joaquin Phoenix doesn't win the Oscar for best actor and 'Joker' doesn't win at the VERY least, best screenplay, it will be one of the biggest Oscar snubs of our time</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Joaquin Phoenix" polarity="positive" from="3" to="18"/>
			<aspectTerm term="screenplay" polarity="positive" from="104" to="114"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="819">
		<text>It's very good I liked it It's Good film Very good</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="844">
		<text>A storyline so full of plot holes, I considered it an insult to my intelligence.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="storyline" polarity="negative" from="2" to="11"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="456">
		<text>It was amazing but I couldn't recreate it at home, I feel sorry for anyone who didn't see this at the cinema, it was just amazing and spun me right out in such a good way!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="159">
		<text>This movie made me want to be a director and create film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="219">
		<text>All these good reviews they must have watched a different movie than I did.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="673">
		<text>I can't remember much else from that other than a scene on a wall ( that might of been the third I don't know , I watch all three in next to each other )</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="scene on a wall" polarity="neutral" from="50" to="65"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1115">
		<text>So bad, so bored, and really, the draws just scared me, they are so horrible in many ways .</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="draws" polarity="negative" from="34" to="39"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="462">
		<text>This is the first and maybe last review I'll ever write.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="155">
		<text>There are so many iconic lines and moments throughout the movie that have been replicated and entrenched in culture over the years.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="lines" polarity="positive" from="25" to="30"/>
			<aspectTerm term="moments" polarity="positive" from="35" to="42"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="378">
		<text>GOOD MOVIE FOR ME AFTER AVATAR SO THANKS SO I HOPE THEY MAKE SECOND EDITIN</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="331">
		<text>the story lacks logic in parts and the final sequence is a little too much.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="negative" from="4" to="9"/>
			<aspectTerm term="final sequence" polarity="negative" from="39" to="53"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="982">
		<text>I loved the story of this film, based on true event this make the film very intersting.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="12" to="17"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="55">
		<text>Following the first half hour, however, it has already stated everything that it has to say.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="first half hour" polarity="positive" from="14" to="29"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="461">
		<text>Nolan this is your masterpiece &amp; best ever.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="795">
		<text>I had watched this movie many times and still want to watch it again cause its so wonderful movie</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="183">
		<text>The only standout that I see is Brando's incredible acting.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Brando's incredible acting" polarity="positive" from="32" to="58"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1145">
		<text>The movie also teaches us to keep our original heart and kindness.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1010">
		<text>It might be a brilliantly made movie but it has played with real historical characters and mixed them up with fictional characters.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="fictional characters" polarity="negative" from="110" to="130"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="308">
		<text>This is definitely one of my favorite movies -- it makes me cry and laugh and ache inside all at once.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="423">
		<text>One of the best movies i have ever seen in my life!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="513">
		<text>Acting, Cinematography, Music, Screenplay, Costumes, Gotham etc everything is 10/10.Oscar worthy performanceby by Joaquin Phoenix.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Acting" polarity="positive" from="0" to="6"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Cinematography" polarity="positive" from="8" to="22"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Music" polarity="positive" from="24" to="29"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Screenplay" polarity="positive" from="31" to="41"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Costumes" polarity="positive" from="43" to="51"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Gotham etc" polarity="positive" from="53" to="63"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Joaquin Phoenix" polarity="positive" from="114" to="129"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="221">
		<text>How can such a movie be rated that high? Will always be a secret to me.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="685">
		<text>This movie run time is just to long for me plus im only posting this review to clear my things to do on IMDb.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="80">
		<text>Really bad movie for me!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="287">
		<text>Popcorn and coke were good.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="193">
		<text>Marlon Brando is excellent though.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Marlon Brando" polarity="positive" from="0" to="13"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="409">
		<text>We assumed whoever wrote this had eaten some mushrooms because it is utterly insane and yet takes itself so seriously.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="991">
		<text>Really shows the cruel and brutal part of the world with a fantastic and intriguing story.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="84" to="89"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="416">
		<text>Completely noisy trash that contained slow motion special effects as its only redeeming quality.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="special effects" polarity="positive" from="50" to="65"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="369">
		<text>A cool looking package, but sometimes less is more!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="893">
		<text>This movie amounts to a melange of violence against a plot of nothing.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="54" to="58"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="834">
		<text>It had the worst ending ever u waste couple of hrs for an endless story,</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="negative" from="17" to="23"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="negative" from="66" to="71"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="42">
		<text>A lot of people have paid their dues in the crazy department, and this would be ultimately ho-hum, although a beautifully made and acted movie.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="made" polarity="positive" from="122" to="126"/>
			<aspectTerm term="acted" polarity="positive" from="131" to="136"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="54">
		<text>I started out enjoying this film immensely.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1045">
		<text>Gradiater was so cool.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1043">
		<text>a caesar fighting a gladiator in the arena!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="961">
		<text>The story comes before the name of the actors involved.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="4" to="9"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="132">
		<text>Everything you need to know is in the title.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1105">
		<text>Art house movies aren't my thing really so I struggle with this sort of thing regardless of where it has been made.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Art house movies" polarity="negative" from="0" to="16"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="201">
		<text>Its appeal confuses me and I like most popular movies.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1092">
		<text>Why this modern day soap opera even won the best picture at oscars its a no no in a million years for me.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="955">
		<text>The city of god is a genius film, genius director, it really gives an insight into the life of Brazilian crime.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="director" polarity="positive" from="41" to="49"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="832">
		<text>Full of stupid guessing provocations.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="788">
		<text>Oh my god this movie is so wonderful. just finished watching on hotstar premium.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="282">
		<text>Multiple endings were irritating.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Multiple endings" polarity="negative" from="0" to="16"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="347">
		<text>Really this film is simply a string of cliches and is mediocre in every way.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="667">
		<text>The battle scenes were not bad either.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="battle scenes" polarity="neutral" from="4" to="17"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="486">
		<text>The acting, cinematography, sound design, and the script itself is phenomenal.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="4" to="10"/>
			<aspectTerm term="cinematography" polarity="positive" from="12" to="26"/>
			<aspectTerm term="sound design" polarity="positive" from="28" to="40"/>
			<aspectTerm term="script" polarity="positive" from="50" to="56"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="258">
		<text>How can anyone who has read the books think this is a good adaptation?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="106">
		<text>I feel that ''The Dark Knight'' is and will be the best Batman movie ever made.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="166">
		<text>Beautifully filmed and written, it is like reading a great novel, the heroes are villains but you get so lost in the story it doesn't matter, it is a prime example of the art of movie making, perhaps the best.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="filmed" polarity="positive" from="12" to="18"/>
			<aspectTerm term="written" polarity="positive" from="23" to="30"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="117" to="122"/>
			<aspectTerm term="movie making" polarity="positive" from="178" to="190"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="81">
		<text>When the movie was half way through all my friends wanted to turn it off. I refused because I had heard it was a fantastic ending.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="516">
		<text>I felt as a privileged person to sit in a movie theater and watching it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1061">
		<text>Good movie, interesting story line, but never in a million years could win a oscar for best movie of the year.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story line" polarity="positive" from="24" to="34"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1067">
		<text>It is an average movie but with a slightly better storyline.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="storyline" polarity="positive" from="50" to="59"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="476">
		<text>Quite possibly one of the greatest pieces of film of the decade? Century?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="450">
		<text>This movie dives deep into these ideas and gives a complex and adventurous route through time and space.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="562">
		<text>There are better films than Matrix, but is still a good movie without any doubts!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="253">
		<text>An emotionally outstanding conclusion to a trilogy already outstandingly perfect</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="conclusion" polarity="positive" from="27" to="37"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="866">
		<text>I only saw a bored and weak plot, nothing new, all time with this kind of movies is marketing, I am getting bored with super heroes movies, even more action parts are so simples</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="28" to="32"/>
			<aspectTerm term="action parts" polarity="negative" from="150" to="162"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="275">
		<text>I hate these movies. End of discussion.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="146">
		<text>So a tongue-in-cheek Joker (Jack Nicholson) goes well with the tongue-in-cheek corny plot.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Jack Nicholson" polarity="positive" from="28" to="42"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="934">
		<text>A very powerful story with the most artistic imagination to recreate it.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="16" to="21"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1094">
		<text>The first of the movie was awesome, but the end is absurd</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="The first of the" polarity="positive" from="0" to="16"/>
			<aspectTerm term="end" polarity="negative" from="44" to="47"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="862">
		<text>The visualization is really impressive. But the story sucks.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="visualization" polarity="positive" from="4" to="17"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="negative" from="48" to="53"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="765">
		<text>A love so pure, so present, so forever!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="368">
		<text>A movie that has too much going on for its own good.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="260">
		<text>It's a shame that Fran Walsh and Peter Jackson succumbed to the trend to Hollywoodize everything adapted for the big screen.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Fran Walsh" polarity="negative" from="18" to="28"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Peter Jackson" polarity="negative" from="33" to="46"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="633">
		<text>It was visually stimulating and action-packed. But... I would have liked a bit of editing in this film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="521">
		<text>The character doesn't even stay true to the comics and the director flat out said it didn't, and then they made it seem like it was part of Gothams fall and he was just a little boy that had a laughing problem.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="character" polarity="negative" from="4" to="13"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="411">
		<text>This abortion should have remained in the trash can.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="432">
		<text>Don't know what's worse, the pathethic acting from almost everyone (Damon won the price tho for insignificant character) or the robots with graphics similar to &quot;Cop&quot; from 1988. HOW can so much people enjoyed this?</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="negative" from="39" to="45"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="349">
		<text>As far as prison movies go, this suffers from an identity crisis is.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="457">
		<text>Interstellar is an experience beyond all experiences.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="98">
		<text>Closest thing we will ever get to a perfect superhero movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="632">
		<text>I saw Two Towers yesterday with my 9 yr. old and 12 yr. old.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="530">
		<text>Nobody really cares that much about some random dude who is as ineloquent and uninspired as the joker is.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="joker" polarity="negative" from="96" to="101"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="144">
		<text>If the plot had been serious, then Ledger's character would have been appropriate.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="733">
		<text>It's just a masterpiece, everything is looking pretty good!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="93">
		<text>Definetly not in the top 100 movies of all time! Are you mad</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="732">
		<text>The cast was phenomenal and I think every superhero got to have their spotlight.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="cast" polarity="positive" from="4" to="8"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="870">
		<text>No acting!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="negative" from="3" to="9"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="355">
		<text>Out of my top 5 worst movies this would be in at least the top 3 movies I hate.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="815">
		<text>I'm actually watching it again right now because it's been a while.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="413">
		<text>Save yourself, watch literally anything else.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="244">
		<text>A must see for any fantasy fan.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="491">
		<text>They need the dignity and respect, coz that is what it takes to be a human.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="731">
		<text>I'll miss all of them together, fighting as one And some parts brought me to tears.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="986">
		<text>Not only guns, photography can also change life.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="56">
		<text>For the remainder of the film it merely repeats itself over and over and over and over. To write more on the film would be to commit the same sin.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="remainder" polarity="negative" from="8" to="17"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="370">
		<text>Great actors, great story, great action! But something's off i dont know what.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="actors" polarity="positive" from="6" to="12"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="20" to="25"/>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="positive" from="33" to="39"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="269">
		<text>Okay, so they do have some really good animations and fighting scenes, but is it really what Lord Of The Rings is about?</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="animations" polarity="positive" from="39" to="49"/>
			<aspectTerm term="fighting scenes" polarity="positive" from="54" to="69"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="177">
		<text>The dialouges are very comfortable.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="dialouges" polarity="positive" from="4" to="13"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="625">
		<text>The problem is, for every 3 minutes I loved, there was a minute I hated.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="972">
		<text>Gives the worst image of poverty people.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="image of poverty people" polarity="negative" from="16" to="39"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="292">
		<text>Peter Jackson's Tolkien adaptations are all among the worst literary adaptations ever. For Tolkien fans they are a torment.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Peter Jackson's Tolkien adaptations" polarity="negative" from="0" to="35"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="288">
		<text>I feel like I'm on another planet when I hear people talk about this movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="917">
		<text>Acting though was quit good even if the acting was all CGI. And, the ending???? WTF!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Acting" polarity="positive" from="0" to="6"/>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="negative" from="69" to="75"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="114">
		<text>This movie is the modern day Godfather, let alone being the best superhero movie of all time.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1071">
		<text>What a shame Parasite won the Oscars instead of 1917. I was expected a masterpiece and felt really disappointed.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="813">
		<text>Very good movie by the creative David Fincher that spot on the intime relation of two married man and woman!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="David Fincher" polarity="positive" from="32" to="45"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="460">
		<text>Our existence, purpose, Universe, life, love &amp; the purpose of it all.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="708">
		<text>Im happy to see finale like that , goodbye Avengers ;(</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="478">
		<text>This is a movie that only those who have felt alone and isolated can truly relate to it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1080">
		<text>Briefly not what I was expected at all.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="397">
		<text>However, it would be good if the movie is short ( 90 t0 100 minutes).</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="160">
		<text>Everyone's acting was perfect.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="11" to="17"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="27">
		<text>it's at times rambling, silly and disjointed. Especially toward the end.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="end" polarity="negative" from="68" to="71"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1022">
		<text>the fight scenes were excellent.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="the fight scenes" polarity="positive" from="0" to="16"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="956">
		<text>Some of the actors are 5*, great sconces and setting.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="sconces" polarity="positive" from="33" to="40"/>
			<aspectTerm term="setting" polarity="positive" from="45" to="52"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="663">
		<text>Did anyone that has read the books see Tolkin's world in TTT?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="76">
		<text>A good contrast is with &quot;Sixth Sense;&quot; the twist makes you look back at the film with even more interest.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="twist" polarity="positive" from="43" to="48"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1104">
		<text>Only an aversion to the main characters.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="main characters" polarity="negative" from="24" to="39"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="738">
		<text>For many years I have been watching every story of Marvel, the last one with a lot of interest.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="558">
		<text>It was quite boring to watch and contained no groundbreaking notions or idea.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="notions" polarity="negative" from="61" to="68"/>
			<aspectTerm term="idea" polarity="negative" from="72" to="76"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1005">
		<text>It's a good movie. Slow, dark &amp; dreary.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1154">
		<text>One of Myozaki's best movies!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="109">
		<text>Christopher Nolan's dark knight is still one of the best superhero movies if not the best.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1063">
		<text>Story line is good but not something new.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Story line" polarity="positive" from="0" to="10"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="107">
		<text>This is literally the best movie I have ever seen!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="888">
		<text>Fight after fight after fight with no one winning.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="181">
		<text>Even though it was a good movie, I see very little that makes it great.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="838">
		<text>The plot is painful.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="4" to="8"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1107">
		<text>Not expecting the events turn into such madness.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="284">
		<text>Women's roles were disgraceful.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Women's roles" polarity="negative" from="0" to="13"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="951">
		<text>Amazing writing, directing, acting, and cinematography.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="writing" polarity="positive" from="8" to="15"/>
			<aspectTerm term="directing" polarity="positive" from="17" to="26"/>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="28" to="34"/>
			<aspectTerm term="cinematography" polarity="positive" from="40" to="54"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="147">
		<text>Nicholson and Keaton for me.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Nicholson" polarity="positive" from="0" to="9"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Keaton" polarity="positive" from="14" to="20"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1088">
		<text>If you didn't know what was going to happen you need to probably read some books or watch more movies.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="336">
		<text>It tells us as much about what prison is really like as Pretty Woman tells us about what prostitution is really like. People like fairy tales, so both these movies were very popular. awful.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="623">
		<text>I´m really angry and hurt with this.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="936">
		<text>This film is unique and extremely excellent.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="820">
		<text>Amazing movie, perfectly casted and with a great storyline.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="casted" polarity="positive" from="25" to="31"/>
			<aspectTerm term="storyline" polarity="positive" from="49" to="58"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="782">
		<text>The direction made the story better than that wrote in the book.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="direction" polarity="positive" from="4" to="13"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="794">
		<text>One of the best movies I have ever seen!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="8">
		<text>Brad Pitt and Edward Norton are best choices for this movie without no doubt.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Brad Pitt" polarity="positive" from="0" to="9"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Edward Norton" polarity="positive" from="14" to="27"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="630">
		<text>Visually alright the effects are not a good reason for a Lord of the Rings fan to attempt to draw in non-fans or undecideds as I was.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Visually" polarity="neutral" from="0" to="8"/>
			<aspectTerm term="effects" polarity="negative" from="21" to="28"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="481">
		<text>But truly, this movie should encourage each and every one of us to become a better person, treat everyone with respect and make each other feel like they belong in this world, instead of making them feel isolated.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="825">
		<text>One of the most brilliant transcripts, I've enjoyed every minute of the movie.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="transcripts" polarity="positive" from="26" to="37"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="212">
		<text>Although the acting can be very good in some parts, the acting in other parts is downright terrible.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="neutral" from="13" to="19"/>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="neutral" from="56" to="62"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="165">
		<text>I must have watched this movie 30 times, yet it is interesting and enjoyable every time.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1161">
		<text>I highly recommend this to anyone of any age.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="367">
		<text>While the beginning was a little too slow for my liking, the movie did very well in terms of it's themes and foreshadowing, making the ending very effective.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="beginning" polarity="negative" from="10" to="19"/>
			<aspectTerm term="themes" polarity="positive" from="98" to="104"/>
			<aspectTerm term="foreshadowing" polarity="positive" from="109" to="122"/>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="positive" from="135" to="141"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="582">
		<text>Being awed by such superb visual effects and intriguing story while feeling guilty and depressed at the atrocious level of violence in &quot;The Matrix&quot; made my movie going experience fall flat.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="visual effects" polarity="positive" from="26" to="40"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="56" to="61"/>
			<aspectTerm term="violence" polarity="negative" from="123" to="131"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="384">
		<text>So fake so pretentious so arrogant so little.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="433">
		<text>The first two hours is a total sleepfest, until the twist at the end where at least something happen that's interesting and not pointless.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="first two hours" polarity="negative" from="4" to="19"/>
			<aspectTerm term="twist at the end" polarity="positive" from="52" to="68"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="447">
		<text>What this movie did to me was crazy.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="668">
		<text>In general, it was a faint movie from the other two films.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="other two" polarity="positive" from="42" to="51"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="466">
		<text>I love how the music and the sound design give me immersion to the full history of Interstellar, I simply love it so much, great experience to watch.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="music" polarity="positive" from="15" to="20"/>
			<aspectTerm term="sound design" polarity="positive" from="29" to="41"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="681">
		<text>The first Ring-Movie was exciting and it made me curious about part two. But after watching part two I decided not to watch part 3!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="first Ring-Movie" polarity="positive" from="4" to="20"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="818">
		<text>This is a great movie It's well written and focused on the plot ,keeps you thinking and on the edge of your seat, there's not movies like this out there</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="written" polarity="positive" from="32" to="39"/>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="positive" from="59" to="63"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="559">
		<text>It is a film that has done well due to the time it was released.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="616">
		<text>The quality of the story and the visuals are still the top after 20 years</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="19" to="24"/>
			<aspectTerm term="visuals" polarity="positive" from="33" to="40"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="173">
		<text>A work of art that will be remembered forever, and I admire the acting.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="64" to="70"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1158">
		<text>A pure work of art.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="506">
		<text>I have no doubt it will win multiple oscars.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="750">
		<text>The first time I watched I cried, it's a truly inspiring movie that is relatable to anyone even if they don't have cancer.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1035">
		<text>Definitely a much watch if you are a fan of Russell Crowe!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="686">
		<text>So i looked for a movie i really dislike to bash it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="372">
		<text>Not my type, although i lobe ellen page.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="170">
		<text>And it lives to the hype, everyone should see this movie at some point.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="265">
		<text>I didn´t like this movie, because it´s story is pretty much based on Clichés, and the target for it are children with 14 yrs - less.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="negative" from="39" to="44"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="401">
		<text>I use this and Lucy with the exact same problems ,when having a rant about how terrible movies/tv are getting</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Lucy" polarity="negative" from="15" to="19"/>
			<aspectTerm term="movies/tv" polarity="neutral" from="88" to="97"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="909">
		<text>Grass grow in my back yard.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="112">
		<text>1. Batman Returns 2. The Dark Knight 3. Batman An absolute Classic!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="607">
		<text>Watched again recently and still stands up as one of the best movies ever!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="395">
		<text>Just now I've watched the movie on Prime Video. I thought it'll be good movie but isn't.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="314">
		<text>The actors are brilliant, the writing was awesome!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="actors" polarity="positive" from="4" to="10"/>
			<aspectTerm term="writing" polarity="positive" from="30" to="37"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="580">
		<text>Matrix has not much: a weak plot, spotty acting, and canned dialog.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="28" to="32"/>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="negative" from="41" to="47"/>
			<aspectTerm term="dialog" polarity="negative" from="60" to="66"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1026">
		<text>Such a good story and some really good fight scenes</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="12" to="17"/>
			<aspectTerm term="fight scenes" polarity="positive" from="39" to="51"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="131">
		<text>A mediocre thriller is way better than this CGI garbage!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="CGI" polarity="negative" from="44" to="47"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="921">
		<text>I later read that everything is &quot;real&quot; - they shot it there in the favelas.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="126">
		<text>Ultra cheese-fest it's like a bad network television show lmao.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="728">
		<text>We know this most best selling movie of all time.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="621">
		<text>He sold everything to the mainstream bad taste.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="404">
		<text>I did not enjoy the story line or the character's goals and ghost.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story line" polarity="negative" from="20" to="30"/>
			<aspectTerm term="goals" polarity="negative" from="50" to="55"/>
			<aspectTerm term="ghost" polarity="negative" from="60" to="65"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="85">
		<text>You might need more than a little MENTAL HELP; if YOU LIKE THIS MOVIE.... mentally people would want the time spent watching this movie back.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="249">
		<text>Peter Jackson outdoes himself in this stunning adaptation of the finale of J.R.R. Tolkein's The Lord of the Rings trilogy.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Peter Jackson" polarity="positive" from="0" to="13"/>
			<aspectTerm term="J.R.R" polarity="neutral" from="75" to="80"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Tolkein" polarity="neutral" from="82" to="89"/>
			<aspectTerm term="The Lord of the Rings trilogy" polarity="neutral" from="92" to="121"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="691">
		<text>Even the more interesting characters become boring in such a context.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="characters" polarity="negative" from="26" to="36"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="240">
		<text>A great ending to the series</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="positive" from="8" to="14"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="153">
		<text>This film is pretty much the perfection of the craft.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="650">
		<text>Fun adventure movie with the addition of a great character in Gollum.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="character" polarity="positive" from="49" to="58"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Gollum" polarity="positive" from="62" to="68"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="670">
		<text>It is action packed, fantasy filled and thoroughly exciting.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="245">
		<text>would definitely recommend to watch it with ur family n friends</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="688">
		<text>My least favorite Christmas treat for my family was the film Lord of the Rings-Two Towers, which I found excruciatingly too long.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="141">
		<text>It was an awfull movie! i don't recommented at all</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="561">
		<text>When I was younger, around 8-10 yo, I think, I used to like Matrix, his dodges and the action etc.. But today.. In 2018 the film doesn't look as good as his Rating.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="dodges" polarity="positive" from="72" to="78"/>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="positive" from="87" to="93"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="993">
		<text>Seriously the best fantasy film of the modern area with great acting and emotional rollercoastering all the way through.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="62" to="68"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="188">
		<text>I don't care how much other people may like it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="18">
		<text>This is one of my favorites.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="568">
		<text>Add to this the fact that it stars Keanu Reeves, surely one of the worst dramatic actors of all time.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Keanu Reeves" polarity="negative" from="35" to="47"/>
			<aspectTerm term="actors" polarity="negative" from="82" to="88"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1018">
		<text>The gladiator scenes were, of course, stunning, it's just a shame that the movie tries too hard to be &quot;I Claudius&quot; in-between.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="gladiator scenes" polarity="positive" from="4" to="20"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="150">
		<text>I hate batman I like superman Batman sucks So 2 star</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="batman" polarity="negative" from="7" to="13"/>
			<aspectTerm term="superman" polarity="positive" from="21" to="29"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Batman" polarity="negative" from="30" to="36"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1031">
		<text>Familiar Hollywood epic legend, but it has to be said that its production level is excellent.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="production level" polarity="positive" from="63" to="79"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="151">
		<text>One of the best films of all time, an absolute masterpiece.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1132">
		<text>The story is about a little girl named Chihiro and her family, they are moving to a brand new house.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="176">
		<text>This is not just movie, it is an emotion.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="407">
		<text>Jesus his movie is a TRAIN WRECK it has an amazing cast don't get me wrong but that's the only good part stay far away from this</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="cast" polarity="positive" from="51" to="55"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1036">
		<text>This is such a great movie about the abuse of power, true leaders, fight for justice, I could go on forever!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="157">
		<text>A flawless movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="687">
		<text>The Lord of the rings series suck!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="985">
		<text>It wasn't dragged out or boring and the story is somewhat believable!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="neutral" from="40" to="45"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="959">
		<text>As a Brazilian filmmaker myself, I attest that Cidade de Deus (City of God) still is, 17 years after its release, the best film we've ever made.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="105">
		<text>This film is the bar when it comes to superhero movies.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1109">
		<text>Too much conspiracy. for a low budget movie .</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="budget" polarity="neutral" from="31" to="37"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1006">
		<text>Action too gory.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Action" polarity="negative" from="0" to="6"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="306">
		<text>But in this case, the movie is so much better, I like the end more than in the book.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="end" polarity="positive" from="58" to="61"/>
			<aspectTerm term="book" polarity="negative" from="79" to="83"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="522">
		<text>Don't waste 2 hours of your life this movie is the baddest i've seen in a long time.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="715">
		<text>LITERALLY , one of the best movies i have seen in my entire life , filled with a tone of action and emotions .</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="positive" from="89" to="95"/>
			<aspectTerm term="emotions" polarity="positive" from="100" to="108"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="69">
		<text>it takes it a bit far though bc of the whole towers collapsing at the end bit. that was a bit much.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="towers collapsing at the end bit" polarity="negative" from="45" to="77"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="231">
		<text>Expected end.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="end" polarity="neutral" from="9" to="12"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1111">
		<text>Interesting plot, held my attention throughout most of the movie, although rather long.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="positive" from="12" to="16"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="657">
		<text>Awesome Movie!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="215">
		<text>I feelt so sleeping while watchin it and felt that I just wasted two hours watching it and decided to stop</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="427">
		<text>During the whole movie I felt the like they bullshiting me.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="273">
		<text>Generally not a fan of Lord of the Rings.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="272">
		<text>Horrible commercial trash.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="373">
		<text>this movie is too blank, don't like nolan</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="nolan" polarity="negative" from="36" to="41"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1160">
		<text>It's well-developed with humor mixed with action mixed with fairytale and more.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1028">
		<text>great acting and a story line you can follow i rate it a 8/10 . defiantly one to watch.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="6" to="12"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story line" polarity="positive" from="19" to="29"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="396">
		<text>The movie is very long and the real concept of movie starts after 1 hour.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="281">
		<text>Waste of my time and money (and the studio's).</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="576">
		<text>Many of the effects in this movie have been copied over and over.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="effects" polarity="neutral" from="12" to="19"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="779">
		<text>I'm too late to watch this.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="218">
		<text>One of the most boring movies I have ever watched.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="641">
		<text>The battle scene in the last hour is very well done.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="battle scene in the last hour" polarity="positive" from="4" to="33"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="262">
		<text>What is wrong with ending?</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="negative" from="19" to="25"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="511">
		<text>That what's made the movie,,, the oscar winner actor made a new joker rivalry with heath ledger joker, better joker in some people opinion.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="heath ledger joker" polarity="positive" from="83" to="101"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1053">
		<text>The narrative and the actors were excellent.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="narrative" polarity="positive" from="4" to="13"/>
			<aspectTerm term="actors" polarity="positive" from="22" to="28"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="776">
		<text>And this movie is recommended for all to watch cause there is things to learn from this movie!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="689">
		<text>the fanny factor kicked in after the first two hours and except for the scenery and special effects, I found this just plain boring - the one with the most charisma in the film was that talking tree!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="scenery" polarity="positive" from="72" to="79"/>
			<aspectTerm term="special effects" polarity="positive" from="84" to="99"/>
			<aspectTerm term="talking tree" polarity="positive" from="186" to="198"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="110">
		<text>I think this is the first movie that villain become more attracted by Fans more than the hero,he really gives the better class of criminal the movie needed.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="villain" polarity="positive" from="37" to="44"/>
			<aspectTerm term="hero" polarity="negative" from="89" to="93"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="323">
		<text>People are just hyped because it is in #1 . And I don't think those people have seen a lot of movies .</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="931">
		<text>I had no idea what it was about going into it, and the rawness and humanity of it really hit me as I watched it for the first time.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="394">
		<text>A very boring film, too long and without any emotion, very bad.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="122">
		<text>This movie was so lame.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="581">
		<text>The basic premise of the movie is compelling, but now that the special effects have slipped from groundbreaking to ordinary, this thing doesn't offer much.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="premise" polarity="positive" from="10" to="17"/>
			<aspectTerm term="special effects" polarity="negative" from="63" to="78"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="379">
		<text>Ummm, I think I need to rewatch it when I'm not so tired.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="612">
		<text>A must watch movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="531">
		<text>The hype portraying the movie as painful and cruel is just cringe.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="hype" polarity="negative" from="4" to="8"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="682">
		<text>Extremely boring and long movie with poor storyline.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="storyline" polarity="negative" from="42" to="51"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="619">
		<text>Why oh why haven't film makers made more modern day sequels to this great film?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1042">
		<text>Once more Hollywood mistake,they can't figure out the end without a spectacle.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="end" polarity="negative" from="54" to="57"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="465">
		<text>I like this movie quite a lot.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="545">
		<text>No doubt Oscar winning stuff.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="60">
		<text>DEFINITELY not one that I would see again.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="792">
		<text>Never cried more, amen Saddest movie ever made, I think my boyfriend cried too WARNING: do not watch on your period</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="333">
		<text>I wait for the day when this film is no longer in the top 200 of IMDb, as it deserves.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="354">
		<text>It is one of the worst movies I have ever seen in my life.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1012">
		<text>It follows the journey of one man and is quite tight with no detours or distractions.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="182">
		<text>The movie is long, and often long winded.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="554">
		<text>This was just the same idea played over over and over.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="889">
		<text>Its like every other superhero movie...nothing special and waaaay to over hyped!!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="758">
		<text>The perspective that this film tries to influence about living, the meaning of life and death, of enjoying every moment and doing what really matters is interesting.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="82">
		<text>We saw the movie through, but it only got worse.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="45">
		<text>This film starts out good then it just disappoints.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="534">
		<text>At first feel pity for the guy suffering, but he lacks charm and then well he is just a killer.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1021">
		<text>definitely a big screen viewer.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="615">
		<text>A classic for the generation.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1004">
		<text>The battle scenes are terrific, but don't just watch it for that, watch it for the fights and the acting.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="The battle scenes" polarity="positive" from="0" to="17"/>
			<aspectTerm term="fights" polarity="positive" from="83" to="89"/>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="98" to="104"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="821">
		<text>A unexpected twist that keeps you interested!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="twist" polarity="positive" from="13" to="18"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="949">
		<text>great actors. great director. great setting</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="actors" polarity="positive" from="6" to="12"/>
			<aspectTerm term="director" polarity="positive" from="20" to="28"/>
			<aspectTerm term="setting" polarity="positive" from="36" to="43"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="474">
		<text>This was the best Sci-fi movie of the Decade and one of the best Movies of all time</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="227">
		<text>My only complaint was that it went on too long.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="920">
		<text>I really really liked it and everything looked so real.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="362">
		<text>The fatal flow of this movie lies in his betrayal of the same expectation that it builds in the first half.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="betrayal of the same expectation that it builds in the first half" polarity="negative" from="41" to="106"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="449">
		<text>The vast amount of space is always been intriguing and waiting to be discovered.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="713">
		<text>You will not he disappointed</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1016">
		<text>So is right for Gladiator, but dry dialogues and &quot;soap opera&quot; moralisation playing bad joke for this effort.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="dialogues" polarity="negative" from="35" to="44"/>
			<aspectTerm term="moralisation" polarity="negative" from="62" to="74"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="678">
		<text>The movie was so boring I started to check my watch while watching.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="674">
		<text>There must be some kindness in the world, which is worth fighting to the end.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="797">
		<text>10/10 - a uniquely beautiful tearjerker that will get you every single time</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="220">
		<text>Just a bunch of crap and talking which you can hardly understand cuz one guy talks with his mouth full the whole movie and then a lot of Italian.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="talking" polarity="negative" from="25" to="32"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="499">
		<text>W.O.W!!! What can I say about how brilliant Phoenix act performance is ??</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Phoenix act performance" polarity="positive" from="44" to="67"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="962">
		<text>A true diamond.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="898">
		<text>Dear Users, In my experience of last fifty years - this is the worst movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1047">
		<text>The scene he got to ses the king was so exciting.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="The scene he got to ses the king" polarity="positive" from="0" to="32"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="267">
		<text>I can´t understand why it´s so overrated, there isn´t really anything that good on this flick.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="676">
		<text>He is loyal and protective of frodo at all times, even when frodo is seduced by gollum to get rid of Sam.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="634">
		<text>Too Long! Especially too many fight scenes.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="too many fight scenes" polarity="negative" from="21" to="42"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="756">
		<text>A lovely sad story(you're gonna cry).</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="sad story" polarity="positive" from="9" to="18"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="851">
		<text>Ridiculous ridiculous ridiculous plot.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="33" to="37"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="610">
		<text>The characters did an amazing job.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="characters" polarity="positive" from="4" to="14"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="754">
		<text>I just wanna explain what I feel it's just like A knife in our hearts 💔</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="295">
		<text>One of the best dramas of all time!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="998">
		<text>2020 and there are so many action films better than gladiator.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="620">
		<text>Peter Jackson has let down all LOTR fans that believed in him.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Peter Jackson" polarity="negative" from="0" to="13"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="943">
		<text>Wonderful characters, cityscape and views of the city.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="characters" polarity="positive" from="10" to="20"/>
			<aspectTerm term="cityscape" polarity="positive" from="22" to="31"/>
			<aspectTerm term="views of the city" polarity="positive" from="36" to="53"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="324">
		<text>It's way too much overrated in my opinion .</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="488">
		<text>Joaquin Pheonix deserves an Oscar win for this tbh.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Joaquin Pheonix" polarity="positive" from="0" to="15"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1153">
		<text>Give it a chance it is one of my best Japanese movies.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="631">
		<text>All of the matrix movies still dwarf this if you are going to talk Computer animation.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Computer animation" polarity="negative" from="67" to="85"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="13">
		<text>Brad Pitt is very engaging as the fight club 'director'.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Brad Pitt" polarity="positive" from="0" to="9"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="596">
		<text>A good movie to see when you just want to be entertained, without having to think too deeply.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1101">
		<text>This is just a normal movie that explains the rich and poor. That's all.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="535">
		<text>Heath Ledger was far better.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Heath Ledger" polarity="positive" from="0" to="12"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="763">
		<text>I prefer this one than Romeo and Juliet.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="551">
		<text>Promotes hate violence suicide and Murder.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="978">
		<text>I was hesitant to watched this movie at first. But ones I click and started watching, I got hooked up to it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="2">
		<text>It has very good cinematography shots and it is very entertaining.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="cinematography shots" polarity="positive" from="17" to="37"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="785">
		<text>I hope this magic relationships ever happen in real life.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="443">
		<text>This film kept my attention the whole time, I was hesitant to even move during some parts.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="594">
		<text>Superlative special effects, non-stop action, but no real plot, a total disregard for scientific realities, and lots of simplistic &quot;philosophy.&quot;</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="special effects" polarity="positive" from="12" to="27"/>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="neutral" from="38" to="44"/>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="58" to="62"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="849">
		<text>This movie was absolutely horrendous.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="322">
		<text>This is a normal average movie .</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="494">
		<text>In this movie, through joker's life, I begin to get it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="318">
		<text>It's beautiful story!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="15" to="20"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1072">
		<text>It is like watching 2 different movies.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="974">
		<text>Through the means of violence, to express the feelings of compassion, this is the film's greatness.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="664">
		<text>I like the presence of the trees very much.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="trees" polarity="positive" from="27" to="32"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="711">
		<text>I just want to say how amazing this film is from start to finish.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="885">
		<text>Dragged on and on and on.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1059">
		<text>Nothing against Korean movies. Movie is over rated.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="97">
		<text>Just watched Joker in 2019, I just has to come back and give dark knight a 10. And thanks to Heath Ledger for the exceptional performs.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Joker" polarity="negative" from="13" to="18"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Heath Ledger" polarity="positive" from="93" to="105"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="803">
		<text>This is a Good movie is the So dramatic and mysterious I never seen movie like this befor And i feel so sad because Is so underrated Such a good movie like this deserve so much better</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="dramatic" polarity="positive" from="31" to="39"/>
			<aspectTerm term="mysterious" polarity="positive" from="44" to="54"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="62">
		<text>The only redeeming quality of the film was the twist at the end.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="twist at the end" polarity="positive" from="47" to="63"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="762">
		<text>So true to the book.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="61">
		<text>for sure not letting my 16 year old watch it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="127">
		<text>I have a habbit to pick out movies That are a waste of time for me and this was an example for me, I First tried it when I was younger and basically didnt understand That much english and now I am older but still dont understand the fuzz and hype 'round this movie, the only great aspect of It was the joker until the third act and then he became also garbage.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="joker" polarity="negative" from="302" to="307"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="6">
		<text>Many people raved about this movie and I can agree with them.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="937">
		<text>Follows the life of rocket living his life in the city of god, which is full of gangs and a lot of violence.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="798">
		<text>This movie is the best every thing is perfect i dont think i could cry more than this😭😭😭</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="927">
		<text>It simple straight forward &amp; easy to understand.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1085">
		<text>The movie starts of good and seems interesting but eventually it becomes worse as the movie goes on.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1159">
		<text>This is a master piece that will stand the test of time for generations to come, all that surpasses its imagination is its heart wrenching score and beautiful visuals.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="score" polarity="positive" from="139" to="144"/>
			<aspectTerm term="visuals" polarity="positive" from="159" to="166"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="133">
		<text>If you want to see an astounding portrayal of the Joker, then go see Joaquin Phoenix nailing the role in &quot;Joker&quot;.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="portrayal" polarity="positive" from="33" to="42"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Joaquin Phoenix" polarity="positive" from="69" to="84"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="405">
		<text>The girl they paired Leonardo with didn't work.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="girl they paired Leonardo" polarity="negative" from="4" to="29"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="191">
		<text>Maybe I was tired while watching it but anyway I was disappointed.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="973">
		<text>The acting is belivable but the story line is very unengaging and rather boring.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="4" to="10"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story line" polarity="negative" from="32" to="42"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="839">
		<text>The acting wooden.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="negative" from="4" to="10"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="510">
		<text>The reality, far from fiction!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="464">
		<text>If cinema is to be included among the arts, then this is a timeless masterpiece to cherish and Nolan is the Michelangelo of this industry.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Nolan" polarity="positive" from="95" to="100"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="206">
		<text>terrible seeing as everyone holds it in such high regard.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="313">
		<text>It was smart, clever, and brings you inside behind the wall.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="548">
		<text>the film is boring boring boring at the end of the movie I was still waiting for the crimes, thriller scene and drama is bad bad bad.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="350">
		<text>Tries to do too much by not actually doing anything at all story wise.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="negative" from="59" to="64"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="902">
		<text>I don't understand how anyone can watch this and think that it's good.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="77">
		<text>You may even want to see it again.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="293">
		<text>People who say otherwise can either not read or get paid for it</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1125">
		<text>Simplistic plots, adolescent themes, ho-hum animation.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plots" polarity="negative" from="11" to="16"/>
			<aspectTerm term="themes" polarity="negative" from="29" to="35"/>
			<aspectTerm term="animation" polarity="negative" from="44" to="53"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="198">
		<text>very bored after 30 minutes of watching.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="965">
		<text>I love the concept.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="concept" polarity="positive" from="11" to="18"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="438">
		<text>I love how the music and the sound design give me immersion to the full history of Interstellar, I simply love it so much, great experience to watch.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="music" polarity="positive" from="15" to="20"/>
			<aspectTerm term="sound design" polarity="positive" from="29" to="41"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="579">
		<text>You know, once the effects have been copied a hundred times over, a movie has to have something to it to stand up on its own.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="effects" polarity="negative" from="19" to="26"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="310">
		<text>I really loved this movie I watch 2 time actually but it was too long</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="773">
		<text>loved this movie just an awesome adaptation the novel of the same name.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="adaptation the novel" polarity="positive" from="33" to="53"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="441">
		<text>The time concept was especially mind-breaking.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="time concept" polarity="positive" from="4" to="16"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="854">
		<text>I can't believe this piece of s.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="869">
		<text>Typical CGI movie.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="CGI" polarity="neutral" from="8" to="11"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="517">
		<text>Joaquin Phoenix and Todd Phillips gave to the world of cinema a rear pearl.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="505">
		<text>Very dark, grimy and disturbing, exactly how an origin film about the joker should be.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="363">
		<text>When you carefully describe a complex world in a convincing way, you cannot take back your explanation just to provide same old fashioned action.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="neutral" from="138" to="144"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="83">
		<text>I can't see anything uplifting about this movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="467">
		<text>Well, it did go on too long, but I enjoyed the relationships of the fathers and daughters displayed and the black hole he was experiencing that showed various time lines of his past in a sort of rubix cube overhead shot.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="relationships of the fathers and daughters" polarity="positive" from="47" to="89"/>
			<aspectTerm term="black hole he was experiencing that showed various time lines of his past in a sort of rubix cube overhead shot" polarity="positive" from="108" to="219"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="602">
		<text>The action is just so amazing to watch.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="positive" from="4" to="10"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1147">
		<text>This movie makes us learn a lot of things like what is a true friendship, what greed can cause, how much family matters ets.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="618">
		<text>I can't tell a word when I first watch this movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="268">
		<text>Somewhere in the &quot;trilogy&quot;, this book lost it`s content and became an action movie like Terminator or Rambo.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="book" polarity="negative" from="33" to="37"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="617">
		<text>Breathtaking and that is the movie. The Photography,the stun, the storytelling skill,the Geek,the Nerdy,the chasing.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Photography" polarity="positive" from="40" to="51"/>
			<aspectTerm term="stun" polarity="positive" from="56" to="60"/>
			<aspectTerm term="storytelling skill" polarity="positive" from="66" to="84"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Geek" polarity="positive" from="89" to="93"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Nerdy" polarity="positive" from="98" to="103"/>
			<aspectTerm term="chasing" polarity="positive" from="108" to="115"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="970">
		<text>Knowing Portuguese really helps understand the perect dialouge that gives the viewer a real feel for the Rio de Janeiro culture</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1076">
		<text>Oversimplified nonsense, can't believe people are rating so high, it's just another film pretending to outsmart it's audience.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="570">
		<text>Okay, okay, so the movie was mildly entertaining. But #20 on the top 250 films of all time?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="266">
		<text>While the photography, the music and the especial effects are really good, the acting (if there was any) and the history itself are plain lame.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="photography" polarity="positive" from="10" to="21"/>
			<aspectTerm term="music" polarity="positive" from="27" to="32"/>
			<aspectTerm term="especial effects" polarity="positive" from="41" to="57"/>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="negative" from="79" to="85"/>
			<aspectTerm term="history" polarity="negative" from="113" to="120"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="723">
		<text>Time travel in this movie has problem.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Time travel" polarity="negative" from="0" to="11"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="190">
		<text>A film about post war US life.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="564">
		<text>loved the cgi and the cool story line I would recommend this film to allot of people</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="cgi" polarity="positive" from="10" to="13"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story line" polarity="positive" from="27" to="37"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1019">
		<text>By the second or third scene with the Emperor we know that he's thoroughly evil so we don't need it to be re-emphasised again and again.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="383">
		<text>It is really sad to see so many people work so hard to produce this thing.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="593">
		<text>Girl kicks butt, guy saves girls butt, guy and girl like each other's butts.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="64">
		<text>freakiest movie I've ever seen.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="729">
		<text>im already watching this movie more than 2 time. and never get bored</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="679">
		<text>Even the new StarWars movies offer more suspense then this bad second part of the Ring-trilogy.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="second part" polarity="negative" from="63" to="74"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Ring-trilogy" polarity="neutral" from="82" to="94"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="778">
		<text>It makes me want to fall and love and feel this way about someone one day</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1127">
		<text>5/10 ( *IF* I were to watch it again, I would fast forward a lot )</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="574">
		<text>First time seeing it in the theater blew my mind , nothing more than a cautionary tale about the dangers of A.I and our progressing technology.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="129">
		<text>What's all the hype about this movie?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="608">
		<text>The Matrix is one of the best sci-fi movies ever made!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="31">
		<text>Did not feel I am in a theatre displays a dream.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="809">
		<text>This is a great example of engaging, clever and sharp cinema.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="cinema" polarity="positive" from="54" to="60"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="17">
		<text>The story, the screenplay, the acting, everything is well-tuned for good entertainment.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="4" to="9"/>
			<aspectTerm term="screenplay" polarity="positive" from="15" to="25"/>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="31" to="37"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1129">
		<text>A good moral for bratty children and good entertainment and nostalgia for adults.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="moral" polarity="positive" from="7" to="12"/>
			<aspectTerm term="entertainment" polarity="positive" from="42" to="55"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="196">
		<text>Might be a lot of people's favourite but I can't gel with this picture. And I've tried!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="444">
		<text>Amazing soundtrack and visuals.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="soundtrack" polarity="positive" from="8" to="18"/>
			<aspectTerm term="visuals" polarity="positive" from="23" to="30"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="431">
		<text>What a piece of crap!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="325">
		<text>My honest rating would be 7/10</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="142">
		<text>I found this movie particularly annoying mainly because Heath Ledger's monstrously serious Joker doesn't fit in with the corny plot.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Heath Ledger" polarity="neutral" from="56" to="68"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Joker" polarity="negative" from="91" to="96"/>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="127" to="131"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="274">
		<text>I find fantasy to just be uninteresting.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="fantasy" polarity="negative" from="7" to="14"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="742">
		<text>So much of love, your eyes are always glued to the screen.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="340">
		<text>It's so Hollywood cliche !</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="228">
		<text>It should have finished at Mount Doom the rest of the scenes were not necessary.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Mount Doom" polarity="neutral" from="27" to="37"/>
			<aspectTerm term="scenes" polarity="negative" from="54" to="60"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="994">
		<text>The soundtrack by Zimmer really propels this film</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="soundtrack" polarity="positive" from="4" to="14"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="913">
		<text>Story is scandalous.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Story" polarity="negative" from="0" to="5"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="92">
		<text>Maybe it doesn't deserve the 1 I gave it, but I am not pleased with the high rating it has.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="high rating" polarity="negative" from="72" to="83"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="252">
		<text>Really great movie and entertaining. Better than the Hobbits honestly.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Hobbits" polarity="negative" from="53" to="60"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="892">
		<text>This is not Marvel, this is junk!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="802">
		<text>Makes you fear women period lol.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="605">
		<text>There will be no movie like matrix, thanks for the masterpiece !</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="211">
		<text>I felt emotionally disconnected from the movie and constantly found myself checking how long was left.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="492">
		<text>If you don't have that, money will only be a reminder of them being a &quot;good boy&quot;.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="341">
		<text>How can this be in the top 2 best movies ever ? I don't understand it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="899">
		<text>It has no consistent plot - no direction - no editing and most importantly no morale.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="21" to="25"/>
			<aspectTerm term="direction" polarity="negative" from="31" to="40"/>
			<aspectTerm term="editing" polarity="negative" from="46" to="53"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1140">
		<text>This was my first ever Hayao Miyazaki work. It was magical to be frank.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="801">
		<text>Watched it several times and enjoued every minute.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="563">
		<text>Was a very good film back in my day i really loved the charters and the actors!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="charters" polarity="positive" from="55" to="63"/>
			<aspectTerm term="actors" polarity="positive" from="72" to="78"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="254">
		<text>This movie is totally a fiction movie based on some book.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="book" polarity="neutral" from="52" to="56"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1037">
		<text>Great cast. Great storyline.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="cast" polarity="positive" from="6" to="10"/>
			<aspectTerm term="storyline" polarity="positive" from="18" to="27"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="622">
		<text>My only hope is that he returns from money-land and finishes the trilogy with the dignity it deserves.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="trilogy" polarity="positive" from="65" to="72"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="706">
		<text>This is one of the best movies in the m marvel universe, I will never forget this movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="358">
		<text>The first act is pure exposition. Once that's over, the film gets a lot better, even if it never really goes as far with the craziness of the dreamworld as it probably should have.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="first act" polarity="neutral" from="4" to="13"/>
			<aspectTerm term="craziness of the dreamworld" polarity="negative" from="125" to="152"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="799">
		<text>We know the bliss can't last. And so, tears stream down your face during the third act.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="third act" polarity="positive" from="77" to="86"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="387">
		<text>I have tried to watch this film twice now but found it boring and shallow.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="75">
		<text>This is the first film I have seen in which the plot twist utterly and completely destroys the film.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot twist" polarity="negative" from="48" to="58"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="471">
		<text>2001: A Space Odyssey was a lot better IMO.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1074">
		<text>Second half is very boring and ending is even more</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Second half" polarity="negative" from="0" to="11"/>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="negative" from="31" to="37"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="94">
		<text>Confidently directed, dark, brooding, and packed with impressive action sequences and a complex story, The Dark Knight includes a career-defining turn from Heath Ledger as well as other Oscar worthy performances, TDK remains not only the best Batman movie, but comic book movie ever created.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="directed" polarity="positive" from="12" to="20"/>
			<aspectTerm term="action sequences" polarity="positive" from="65" to="81"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="neutral" from="96" to="101"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Heath Ledger" polarity="positive" from="156" to="168"/>
			<aspectTerm term="performances" polarity="positive" from="199" to="211"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1130">
		<text>Beautiful story, really touching and quite strange but definitely worth it.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="10" to="15"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="590">
		<text>Although the head &quot;FBI&quot; agent was hilarious, as was Keanu's kickboxing displays.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="head &quot;FBI&quot; agent" polarity="positive" from="13" to="29"/>
			<aspectTerm term="kickboxing displays" polarity="negative" from="60" to="79"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="237">
		<text>I have always been a have of the LOTR series.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="LOTR series" polarity="neutral" from="33" to="44"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="627">
		<text>not the worst movie ive ever seen but you combine that it wasnt that interesting and the fact that it was over three hours long makes for a mid-level movie.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="over three hours long" polarity="negative" from="106" to="127"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="693">
		<text>I found it boring and at times incredibly cliché and corny.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="44">
		<text>Full of pseudo-morals and anti-consumerism messages, who has the patience for that.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="pseudo-morals" polarity="negative" from="8" to="21"/>
			<aspectTerm term="anti-consumerism messages" polarity="negative" from="26" to="51"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="24">
		<text>I really hated the ending the whole movie was such a great thing but it dosen't deserve 8.8</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="negative" from="19" to="25"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1108">
		<text>The history is fine, but why does it have an disaster ending?</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="negative" from="54" to="60"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="375">
		<text>There were points my attention drifted due to the slow pacing of the film and then it became hard to follow.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="pacing" polarity="negative" from="55" to="61"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1073">
		<text>Second half too surrealistic for my taste</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Second half" polarity="negative" from="0" to="11"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="874">
		<text>It just destroyed the image of the previous Avengers movies.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="939">
		<text>The first ever foreign language film i loved so much, easily in my all time greatest movie's list, each and every frame of the movie is a craftsmanship.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="each and every frame" polarity="positive" from="99" to="119"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="577">
		<text>This movie has excellent action and effects but I found the story too unbelievable to enjoy.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="positive" from="25" to="31"/>
			<aspectTerm term="effects" polarity="positive" from="36" to="43"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="negative" from="60" to="65"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="256">
		<text>they created whole new world and the even the visual effects are awesome according to that time.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="visual effects" polarity="positive" from="46" to="60"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="174">
		<text>It's so wonderful and you see so many familular faces that you see today.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="475">
		<text>Probably the best movie I have ever seen in my whole entire life</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="698">
		<text>What do I say this movie in incredible I started watching marvel movies around when the first avengers movie came out ever sense I seen everyone of them</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="787">
		<text>Such a great love story im so in love with this movie &lt;3 Can't stop crying</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="love story" polarity="positive" from="13" to="23"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="50">
		<text>By the way, I do not care for Brad Pitt.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Brad Pitt" polarity="negative" from="30" to="39"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="418">
		<text>Ignore the hype, it's probably the same crowd who finds GOT the greatest achievement in cinematic arts</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1083">
		<text>But in all fairness I hated Midsommar more.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="298">
		<text>Shawshank Redemption is without a doubt the most uplifting and touching film I have ever seen.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="749">
		<text>Amazing movie It was very nice watching this romantic drama .</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="romantic drama" polarity="positive" from="45" to="59"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="848">
		<text>I believed the hype and was crestfallen.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="891">
		<text>I almost left the theatre half through the show.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1138">
		<text>The first japanese movie i watched. shaked me .</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1057">
		<text>Just won Oscars cz concept was new, but this itself doesn't make it a better movie than Joker.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="11">
		<text>Truly a masterpiece of story telling and a must see.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story telling" polarity="positive" from="23" to="36"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="359">
		<text>The plot is very exciting and philosophical, but I don't like the protagonist's procrastinating love line. It always pulls me back from the intense and exciting plot.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="positive" from="4" to="8"/>
			<aspectTerm term="protagonist's procrastinating love line" polarity="negative" from="66" to="105"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="120">
		<text>Bale imo has been the best Batman since Adam West, the previous Batman movies ( Keen, Kilmer, Clooney) we're junk compared to Bale playing Batman</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Bale" polarity="positive" from="0" to="4"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Adam West" polarity="positive" from="40" to="49"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Keen" polarity="negative" from="80" to="84"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Kilmer" polarity="negative" from="86" to="92"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Clooney" polarity="negative" from="94" to="101"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Bale" polarity="positive" from="126" to="130"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="543">
		<text>Indulgent, pretentious, overly long and very very dull.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="385">
		<text>Well it is supposed to be an action movie and people love it because they just want to have fun for their buck.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="930">
		<text>This is one of the best movies I've seen in quite awhile.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="4">
		<text>I like it but the beginning was very long and slow while the end was all over the place trying to explain everything.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="beginning" polarity="negative" from="18" to="27"/>
			<aspectTerm term="end" polarity="negative" from="61" to="64"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1051">
		<text>After all the hype, I expected something worth watching, not this</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="180">
		<text>Personally, I found this movie to be quite overrated.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1001">
		<text>I watch this movie cuz they told me it was so depressing but it wasn't</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="694">
		<text>I really hated all the pseudo-emotional romance that was put in for no apparent reason.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="pseudo-emotional romance" polarity="negative" from="23" to="47"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="628">
		<text>the movie looked great at times but in a couple of scenes the use of a blue scene was very noticeable</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="blue scene" polarity="negative" from="71" to="81"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="771">
		<text>It's the best romantic Film I have ever seen , the relationship between Augustus and hazel is so beautiful.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="relationship between Augustus and hazel" polarity="positive" from="51" to="90"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="836">
		<text>Lazy plot, especially in the first half.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="5" to="9"/>
			<aspectTerm term="first half" polarity="negative" from="29" to="39"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="642">
		<text>The movie was extremely slow in the first 2+ hours!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="first 2+ hours" polarity="negative" from="36" to="50"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1141">
		<text>So many feelings at once. Sometimes too artsy, serious, wayward.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="740">
		<text>Good movie will watch again very fun easy to watch</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="49">
		<text>This film could have been so much better.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="933">
		<text>Hands down the greatest movie I have ever scene.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="169">
		<text>This movie is often considered the best ever.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="720">
		<text>This is the best movie i ever watch by Marvel production, i think they never gonna pass this movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="65">
		<text>I recommend seeing this at the $1.50 movie because it's worth seeing, but not payin full price.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="485">
		<text>Please enjoy the movie without overthinking it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="136">
		<text>Isn't Batman for kids as well as adults?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="26">
		<text>The acting is solid-especially the three leads and its &quot;message&quot; about violence, feeling trapped and masculine frustration is humorously presented.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="4" to="10"/>
			<aspectTerm term="leads" polarity="positive" from="41" to="46"/>
			<aspectTerm term="&quot;message&quot; about violence" polarity="positive" from="55" to="79"/>
			<aspectTerm term="feeling trapped and masculine frustration" polarity="positive" from="81" to="122"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1065">
		<text>Acting is not that great.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Acting" polarity="negative" from="0" to="6"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="583">
		<text>Unfortunately barely worth the $8.00 per ticket.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="910">
		<text>Damn, what a long drawn out fight to nothing.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="841">
		<text>I watched it all in disbelief at how bad it was.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1052">
		<text>The most original film of 2019 and it is wickedly funny and darkly disturbing all at the same time.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="810">
		<text>Outstanding performances, engaging story and perfect execution.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="performances" polarity="positive" from="12" to="24"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="35" to="40"/>
			<aspectTerm term="execution" polarity="positive" from="53" to="62"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="99">
		<text>There are few movies where you just feel privileged because you get to watch them and are honoured to. This is one of them.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="967">
		<text>I love the fact that everything was seen through the eyes of multiple characters all while being narrated by the director of the film.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="everything was seen through the eyes of multiple characters all while being narrated by the director of the film" polarity="positive" from="21" to="133"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="896">
		<text>This movie is a FAIL on both points.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="377">
		<text>Zimmer as always delivers a pounding soundtrack.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="soundtrack" polarity="positive" from="37" to="47"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="968">
		<text>He did a great job explaining how they grew up.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="789">
		<text>it'll totally blow your mind.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="709">
		<text>Wow, just Wow!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="398">
		<text>It's approximately 2.32 hours which is not good, it irritate you.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="942">
		<text>I thoroughly enjoyed this film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="768">
		<text>i had watched this moive for 3 time at least, this moive inspired me encouraged me evertime. -xiaolin</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="36">
		<text>Blending humor, with action, with drama, with psychological mind games.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="humor" polarity="neutral" from="9" to="14"/>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="neutral" from="21" to="27"/>
			<aspectTerm term="drama" polarity="neutral" from="34" to="39"/>
			<aspectTerm term="psychological mind games" polarity="neutral" from="46" to="70"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="171">
		<text>The Hollywood at its best, with some money and advice taken in from the mob itself.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="88">
		<text>The worst movie i've ever seen How the good actors like brad took some role like this ?</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="brad" polarity="positive" from="56" to="60"/>
			<aspectTerm term="role" polarity="negative" from="71" to="75"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="518">
		<text>I don't know what people are complaining about: this is really something else.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="154">
		<text>Every single aspect of The Godfather is outstanding.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="352">
		<text>Boring Dull No story at all.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="negative" from="15" to="20"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1086">
		<text>Surely not a feel good but kind of a family crime drama.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="523">
		<text>Crappy writing and no good storyline.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="writing" polarity="negative" from="7" to="14"/>
			<aspectTerm term="storyline" polarity="negative" from="27" to="36"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1128">
		<text>The story line isn't up to the mark as high rated in IMDB.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story line" polarity="negative" from="4" to="14"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="501">
		<text>And this movie has a kind of ending which would leave many speechless.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="positive" from="29" to="35"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="722">
		<text>I like all those magic tricks out of from theirs hands and good teams against bad teams.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="magic tricks" polarity="positive" from="17" to="29"/>
			<aspectTerm term="good teams against bad teams" polarity="positive" from="59" to="87"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="528">
		<text>I want these 2 hours of my life back</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="857">
		<text>Disappointing. Simply and enough said. Do not recommend. So boring.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="987">
		<text>Bloody violence, the law of the jungle and a Rio that doesn't appear on postcards at all.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="234">
		<text>Other than that, the characters finished in keeping their classics.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="characters" polarity="positive" from="21" to="31"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="163">
		<text>Whether it's the acting, scenery, pacing or anything else, it's all just so brilliantly executed.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="17" to="23"/>
			<aspectTerm term="scenery" polarity="positive" from="25" to="32"/>
			<aspectTerm term="pacing" polarity="positive" from="34" to="40"/>
			<aspectTerm term="executed" polarity="positive" from="88" to="96"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="479">
		<text>You understand the motive and you feel sorry for the character.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1131">
		<text>I remember the first time I saw this film or when I was in primary school, I only felt that the style of painting was really beautiful.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="style of painting" polarity="positive" from="96" to="113"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1">
		<text>The film is very weird and wacky.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="880">
		<text>This movie made the good cast look stupid and no common sense.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="701">
		<text>And this goes one level better than infinity war, absolutely fantastic.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="496">
		<text>Dare I say better than Heath Ledger?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="588">
		<text>&quot;The Matrix&quot; is too dark, too long, too tangled and too dumb!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="20">
		<text>This movie really makes you think about your life and the daily events that occur.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="739">
		<text>There can't be a better ending. Thank you Marvel.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="positive" from="24" to="30"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Marvel" polarity="positive" from="42" to="48"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="990">
		<text>The first time I came into contact with Brazilian movies, I was really amazed.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1027">
		<text>GOOD MOVIE can be violent at points but all round very good.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="236">
		<text>Viggo Mortenson was good .</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Viggo Mortenson" polarity="positive" from="0" to="15"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="724">
		<text>I never have seen any movie in life that has such a great action and awesome fantasy , I am speechless and all I can say is bravo and will done.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="positive" from="58" to="64"/>
			<aspectTerm term="fantasy" polarity="positive" from="77" to="84"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="15">
		<text>While a great deal of violence is in this picture, it is in a perspective that makes it cartoonish.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="violence" polarity="negative" from="22" to="30"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="235">
		<text>Cant remember what happened that much but I remember it was good so there you are .</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1048">
		<text>No war, no violence, no disaster, it is destined to be an era without heroes.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1060">
		<text>Its an average movie. Don't know why it created this much buzz.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="197">
		<text>This movie is the definition of overrated, it is incredibly slow moving, half of the movie is dark.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="half of the movie" polarity="negative" from="73" to="90"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="400">
		<text>This is modern film making, lets rush through the story with no real substance or character development, such a waste.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="negative" from="50" to="55"/>
			<aspectTerm term="character development" polarity="negative" from="82" to="103"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="223">
		<text>The story is not unique and not interesting.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="negative" from="4" to="9"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="830">
		<text>HORRIBLE ending. Completely ruined the whole movie!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="negative" from="9" to="15"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="442">
		<text>Wonderfully written -- and finally not a trace of unnecessary romance to be found!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="written" polarity="positive" from="12" to="19"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="661">
		<text>Jackson tried(successfully) to create a blockbuster,but even though he claims to be a fun of Tolkin's work,he did not hesitate to humiliate Lord of The Rings!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="386">
		<text>Don't get me wrong - I like action in movies but this is so superfluous and boring.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="38">
		<text>Only gripe with the film is the last shot (which I will not spoil)</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="last shot" polarity="negative" from="32" to="41"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="712">
		<text>This will take you on a emotional ride.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="770">
		<text>It was actually a really good movie</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="512">
		<text>piece of art</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="43">
		<text>Althought the images are very good and the editing is one of the best I have ever seen, the movie made me want to leave the theater after an hour.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="images" polarity="positive" from="14" to="20"/>
			<aspectTerm term="editing" polarity="positive" from="43" to="50"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="118">
		<text>The storyline has as much twisting and turning to it as a flamenco dancer.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="storyline" polarity="positive" from="4" to="13"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="213">
		<text>It does not live up to the hype, for me.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="822">
		<text>Very good movie keeps you involved and on the edge of your seat!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="143">
		<text>This Joker should be in another movie.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Joker" polarity="negative" from="5" to="10"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="901">
		<text>Boring, plot makes no sense, characters make stupid choices, nothing is explained well.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="8" to="12"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1058">
		<text>Over hyped, Mediocre and people reviewing it in mob mentality.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="979">
		<text>its amazing and I will recommend it</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1013">
		<text>This journey is full of emotion, pain and action and the film portrays this all quite wonderfully.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="536">
		<text>Ok, maybe not but they hype surrounding the movie killed it for me.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="hype surrounding the" polarity="negative" from="23" to="43"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="47">
		<text>The first half hour led me to believe it was going to be good.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="first half" polarity="positive" from="4" to="14"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1079">
		<text>Complicated with less meaning.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="meaning" polarity="negative" from="22" to="29"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="489">
		<text>I will stop watching movies if Joaquin Phoenix is not awarded Oscar for his tremendous acting.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Joaquin Phoenix" polarity="positive" from="31" to="46"/>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="87" to="93"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="824">
		<text>This movie reminds you that the Villain roles are the most important roles in the movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="923">
		<text>Every part of the movie has a excitement.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="86">
		<text>If you like this one see Pulp fiction.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="426">
		<text>I cant believe I saw the same movie as the other reviewers which gave him a 10 score.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="199">
		<text>I watched it once (in jail) to see what all the fuss is about. Boring.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1055">
		<text>Class warfare at its best.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Class warfare" polarity="positive" from="0" to="13"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="613">
		<text>Keenu does a great job with the character of Neo.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Keenu" polarity="positive" from="0" to="5"/>
			<aspectTerm term="character of Neo" polarity="positive" from="32" to="48"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="743">
		<text>You don't want to miss a single shot.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="646">
		<text>Unfortunately, I found myself sleeping in the cinema. I should have known that this would happen, because I really disliked the first movie, which I believe is called 'The Fellowship of the Ring'.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="944">
		<text>Nice Story, greet Screenplay and good Cinematography.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Story" polarity="positive" from="5" to="10"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Screenplay" polarity="positive" from="18" to="28"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Cinematography" polarity="positive" from="38" to="52"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="654">
		<text>Whole Story set up in the two towers in really pick's up.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="214">
		<text>not even in my top 1000 movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="337">
		<text>the film is the most cliched in cinematic history and is worthy of no respect. even worse is how it is so flawless yet it still is of no quality.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="cinematic history" polarity="neutral" from="32" to="49"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1054">
		<text>One of the better endings of a movie in quite a while.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="226">
		<text>Very well filmed and acted with amazing sets and scenery.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="filmed" polarity="positive" from="10" to="16"/>
			<aspectTerm term="acted" polarity="positive" from="21" to="26"/>
			<aspectTerm term="sets" polarity="positive" from="40" to="44"/>
			<aspectTerm term="scenery" polarity="positive" from="49" to="56"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="876">
		<text>The fact that this is rated #30 movie of all time is just unfathomable!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="119">
		<text>If you haven't seen it, your not only missing out, you letting one of the Da Vinci's of the film industry pass you by.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="23">
		<text>Good film always encourage to maker to make more good film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="589">
		<text>But kudos to Carrie-Anne Moss who was about the only bright light here.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Carrie-Anne Moss" polarity="positive" from="13" to="29"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="51">
		<text>My husband talked me into this after time and time again saying &quot;I don't want to watch a movie about fighting&quot;, I guess he thought the beginning was better than I thought it was.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="beginning" polarity="negative" from="135" to="144"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="430">
		<text>What a waste of 3 long hours of my life.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="992">
		<text>A incredible fancy film with extrodinary camera placement</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="camera placement" polarity="positive" from="41" to="57"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="327">
		<text>It has a great cast that turns in some good performances, and the story is compelling; however, I always feel so empty after I see it.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="cast" polarity="positive" from="15" to="19"/>
			<aspectTerm term="performances" polarity="positive" from="44" to="56"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="66" to="71"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="357">
		<text>By far one of the worst movies ever</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1106">
		<text>If I knew more about Korean culture it would probably help.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="500">
		<text>The ending is what matters in a movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1087">
		<text>Looks great. Tired plot.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="19" to="23"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1025">
		<text>Russel Crowe isn't one of my favourite actors but he is brilliant in this film.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Russel Crowe" polarity="positive" from="0" to="12"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="251">
		<text>8/10 Fantastic adventure.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="adventure" polarity="positive" from="15" to="24"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="241">
		<text>The scenes are magnificent, the visual effects are shocking, Sam is loyal and loyal, the elven prince is too handsome, magic, adventure, righteousness, greed and innocent love, every character makes me feel real.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="scenes" polarity="positive" from="4" to="10"/>
			<aspectTerm term="visual effects" polarity="positive" from="32" to="46"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Sam" polarity="positive" from="61" to="64"/>
			<aspectTerm term="elven prince" polarity="positive" from="89" to="101"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="852">
		<text>I agree with the review by Tommy Bott, even though I didn't see the movie. I read the book. That was enough.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="book" polarity="negative" from="86" to="90"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="598">
		<text>On another level entirely to any other science fiction film from the last 20 years .</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="796">
		<text>This movie is great it's made me cry I 'll watch it again</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="334">
		<text>Please, if any film was passed over in favor of Gump at the 1995 Oscars--it was the best film of the nineties--PULP FICTION.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="498">
		<text>Creative actor Joaquin creativity embodied the role of the Joker film deserves more than 10</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Joaquin" polarity="positive" from="15" to="22"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="573">
		<text>Hey, did Jim Cameron do this film?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="572">
		<text>A special effects-driven, mindless action movie with a bad script.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="script" polarity="negative" from="59" to="65"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1082">
		<text>A ten year old could figure out the plot twist.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot twist" polarity="negative" from="36" to="46"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="914">
		<text>It really hurts during watching.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="540">
		<text>JP has one and only acting register : the depressed looser, I don't understand the critics he is as mediocre as always.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="JP" polarity="negative" from="0" to="2"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="209">
		<text>Maybe it's a generational thing, or I simply just don't get it, but The Godfather was bland and boring from start to finish.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="344">
		<text>Yes, it was an interesting movie, and it was a good movie, but it was not spectacular enough to receive all the praise which it has.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="3">
		<text>This movie was good but has that its a classic syndrome of being some ones favorite so its a great movie or the best.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="703">
		<text>This film is very, very great and is the end of 10 years of a series of superheroes. Thanks Marvel</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Marvel" polarity="positive" from="92" to="98"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="436">
		<text>Normally, I don't like to watch a movie second time, but I have watched it thrice.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="351">
		<text>Watch Cool Hand Luke instead</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="745">
		<text>Rarely have I seen a movie that &quot;gets&quot; the book it's adapting so well.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="611">
		<text>After watching this movie i had serious doubts about my sense of reality.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="823">
		<text>A wonderfully crafted Villain Character.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Villain Character" polarity="positive" from="22" to="39"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="905">
		<text>Why do people like this garbage?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="437">
		<text>I will watch again for sure, its superb</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="919">
		<text>Brazilians know how to make a good movie or is just this one?</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Brazilians" polarity="positive" from="0" to="10"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="783">
		<text>The love of two people who are counting their days happily.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="229">
		<text>If you enjoy the trilogy, you'll enjoy this movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="999">
		<text>Standard Hollywood blockbusters are rare for their artistic and cultural accomplishments.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="800">
		<text>To borrow their favorite line from Hazel's favorite book: &quot;Pain demands to be felt.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="735">
		<text>Thanks marvel for this amazing ride and the perfect ending</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="marvel" polarity="positive" from="7" to="13"/>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="positive" from="52" to="58"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1064">
		<text>Screen play little slow at times.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Screen play" polarity="negative" from="0" to="11"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="660">
		<text>In my opinion,The Two Towers did not resemble Tolkin's masterpiece at all.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="996">
		<text>the movie is a big, sometimes terrific, show located in a very hypothetical Roman Empire.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="271">
		<text>Nothing new than Star Wars - Return of the Jedi.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1155">
		<text>I love the animation in this movie and the story is so beautifully done!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="animation" polarity="positive" from="11" to="20"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="43" to="48"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="954">
		<text>One of the finest movies brought the favelas to life</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="925">
		<text>You can't be bored while you watch the movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1084">
		<text>Has a good moral but not a good movie to watch.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="moral" polarity="positive" from="11" to="16"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="963">
		<text>This film was introduced to me while in HS and as an adult it still resonates.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="863">
		<text>Marvel is ruining the reputation by putting all the superheroes together without a whole story.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Marvel" polarity="negative" from="0" to="6"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="negative" from="89" to="94"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="366">
		<text>Who can resist the perfect world in the dream, and is willing to judge whether it is reality or dream?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="454">
		<text>I don't give 9 stars because in my opinion the dialogues are not brilliant, like in other Nolan's movies.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="dialogues" polarity="negative" from="47" to="56"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="452">
		<text>I really liked the idea and the plot full of unexpected points and developments.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="idea" polarity="positive" from="19" to="23"/>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="positive" from="32" to="36"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="194">
		<text>I`m not going to say that it`s chicken-feed but from my point view it has artificially created reputation.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="946">
		<text>every actor play best performance on his character.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="719">
		<text>I'm a big fan of MCU.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="MCU" polarity="positive" from="17" to="20"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="932">
		<text>A must watch from Brasil!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="439">
		<text>This film gave a fresh new experience of a space flick.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="774">
		<text>One of the best romantic movies I have seen!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="786">
		<text>10/10 for making a perfect picture in a terrible conditions.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="63">
		<text>what the hell was this movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="714">
		<text>Specially the climax, seriously one of the best climax I have ever seen.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="climax" polarity="positive" from="14" to="20"/>
			<aspectTerm term="climax" polarity="positive" from="48" to="54"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="989">
		<text>Very excellent editing.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="editing" polarity="positive" from="15" to="22"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="702">
		<text>Best superhero movie created ever it has besrt screenplay, story, action and full entertainment like a perfect package</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="screenplay" polarity="positive" from="47" to="57"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="59" to="64"/>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="positive" from="66" to="72"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="997">
		<text>The first part is good but the end is ridiculous how can we believe that an emperor would fight with a gladiator.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="first part" polarity="positive" from="4" to="14"/>
			<aspectTerm term="end" polarity="negative" from="31" to="34"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="873">
		<text>may be the most expensive, dumbest and soulless film ever made</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="791">
		<text>I have only ever restarted several films and watched them again straight away, Bladerunner and The Terminator, are just two of them and then this came along, this is one of my most favourite films of all the time, just excellent.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="332">
		<text>very good movie to watch a must see anytime but NOT all-time #2</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1126">
		<text>I have seen each of the pieces before, and I have seen them executed better.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1017">
		<text>Overall it's much more &quot;Scott&quot; movie after his two previous bids.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="638">
		<text>I see this as just a good film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="402">
		<text>Such as title.Plagiarism is shameful.It is worse to be a scoundrel than not to admit your mistakes.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="757">
		<text>Its full of romantic moment and even some funny moments.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="moment" polarity="positive" from="21" to="27"/>
			<aspectTerm term="moments" polarity="positive" from="48" to="55"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="329">
		<text>the all-time #2 is WAY high for this flick.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="859">
		<text>When I see this movie all I can do is boring and think when this gonna end.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="935">
		<text>I don't think anyone else may taken this story and portrayed it any better.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="555">
		<text>How about that Joker Ballet in the toilet! Hilariously bad.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Joker Ballet" polarity="negative" from="15" to="27"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="115">
		<text>Great and worth to watch, The Dark Knight is as good as everyone says and easily the best superhero film made.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="603">
		<text>I've seen this film 3 times and each time it just gets better.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="557">
		<text>Matrix is quite a dull and uninspired film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="969">
		<text>One of the best movies of the millennia.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="339">
		<text>shockingly horrendous</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="459">
		<text>After that I watched many times on TV &amp; without doubt I have loved it every single time.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1098">
		<text>Despite being advertised.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1122">
		<text>Ik this movie is meant to be really good but the first time I watched it, I was pretty young, I got scared and now anime scar me lowkey.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="22">
		<text>Just love it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="746">
		<text>The main actors do a great job with a tricky subject.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="main actors" polarity="positive" from="4" to="15"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="717">
		<text>' i love you 3000 '</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="726">
		<text>Loved it so much, just can't see a story with so much depth getting better.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="871">
		<text>The plot does not allow for acting. Too bad!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="4" to="8"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="186">
		<text>This movie continues to be praised, but when I rented it I only made it through 45 minutes before I stopped the video.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="139">
		<text>He is no way the most psychotic killer I've seen in a film!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="575">
		<text>When words alone are not enough, let our inspirational poems, cards and books lift your spirit and give you hope, joy and comfort.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="780">
		<text>Was in tears towards the end.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="346">
		<text>Apparently, I'm the only one with this opinion.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="586">
		<text>Interesting premise is beaten to death by unrelenting video game mentality and special effects, clichéd ending.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="premise" polarity="positive" from="12" to="19"/>
			<aspectTerm term="video game mentality" polarity="negative" from="54" to="74"/>
			<aspectTerm term="special effects" polarity="negative" from="79" to="94"/>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="negative" from="104" to="110"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="382">
		<text>I need to watch it again, probably multiple times because there's a lot going on.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="639">
		<text>The acting is fair, and the CGI is some of the best.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="neutral" from="4" to="10"/>
			<aspectTerm term="CGI" polarity="positive" from="28" to="31"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="704">
		<text>You obviously didn't understand the film if you hate it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="526">
		<text>And for all the people with 10/10(the reason why i went) you're a joke.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="people" polarity="negative" from="16" to="22"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="975">
		<text>Powerful film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="629">
		<text>A decent movie, worse than the first in the trilogy and equally not deserving of the hype it has gotten.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1075">
		<text>Its a normal movie not so so good</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="276">
		<text>The short bald guy is fun to watch though.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="short bald guy" polarity="positive" from="4" to="18"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1118">
		<text>It is the worst animation I have ever seen !</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="animation" polarity="negative" from="16" to="25"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="140">
		<text>If you want to watch an absolute nutter at work watch Wolf Creek ( 2movies and two series) this film is the most overrated film of all time.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="277">
		<text>I thought LOTRs couldn't get any more drawn out, with pointless scenes, I was wrong!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="scenes" polarity="negative" from="64" to="70"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="964">
		<text>One of the best films I have ever seen from the cinematography to the story line and more.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="cinematography" polarity="positive" from="48" to="62"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story line" polarity="positive" from="70" to="80"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1137">
		<text>&quot;Shenyin&quot; is an indispensable synonym to the magical world, meaning &quot;hidden by the supernatural&quot;, by its entertainment, or by abduction, forced captive, and disappeared from the human society, the behavior is unknown.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="224">
		<text>I know it's popular to love the movie as a classic piece, but i didn't like it so much</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="37">
		<text>There is something for everyone in this film and there's so many things to notice on repeat viewings.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="108">
		<text>From the acting to the directing and the score just everything about this movie makes it the greatest of all time.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="9" to="15"/>
			<aspectTerm term="directing" polarity="positive" from="23" to="32"/>
			<aspectTerm term="score" polarity="positive" from="41" to="46"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="468">
		<text>It dragged on the one ice planet that makes them age by 7 years every hour.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="68">
		<text>This film is about how every man wants to be brad pitt.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="brad pitt" polarity="positive" from="45" to="54"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="977">
		<text>Personally, I saw this film more as a documentary of the City of God rather than an entertainment film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="507">
		<text>Do yourself a favor and go see it!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="233">
		<text>I do not really understand the end, but anyway.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="end" polarity="negative" from="31" to="34"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="96">
		<text>Great story great acting, thrilling twist.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="6" to="11"/>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="18" to="24"/>
			<aspectTerm term="twist" polarity="positive" from="36" to="41"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="808">
		<text>A thriller packed mind blowing movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="305">
		<text>And that's a things that's never happened to me before, the movie was better than the book.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="book" polarity="neutral" from="86" to="90"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="66">
		<text>very interesting and weird movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="941">
		<text>The best darkest movie ever made.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="716">
		<text>you will love avenger endgame .</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="697">
		<text>It really astounds me that people could consider this film, with it's blatant editing blunders, jumbled plot and unjustifiable changes to the storyline, better than FOTR. It is a good film, but better?</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="editing" polarity="negative" from="78" to="85"/>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="104" to="108"/>
			<aspectTerm term="changes to the storyline" polarity="negative" from="127" to="151"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1062">
		<text>Good but definitely not worth an Oscar for best movie or best director.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="138">
		<text>Not being nasty but I think Heath Ledger got a sympathy vote.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Heath Ledger" polarity="negative" from="28" to="40"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="567">
		<text>Clever this is not, more like pretentious.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="12">
		<text>Fight Club is a laugh fest from beginning to end.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="30">
		<text>Still the whole cinematic experience is not there.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="cinematic experience" polarity="negative" from="16" to="36"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="247">
		<text>Crazy to call this a classic.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="312">
		<text>it's an one of the best movie ever watched.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="908">
		<text>The outcome of dumbing down and treating the audience as morons.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1039">
		<text>Bloody, entertaining, larger than life and beautiful to look at.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="595">
		<text>Great eye candy and no substance combine to give an average film overall.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="445">
		<text>Less than 10 stars is unrealistic. One of the best movies ever.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="307">
		<text>Watch the movie, it is great.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="303">
		<text>This movie is one of the best I have ever seen.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1040">
		<text>While not exactly thought provoking or historically accurate, Ridley Scott's &quot;Gladiator&quot; works remarkably as mainstream hollywood entertainment.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Gladiator" polarity="positive" from="78" to="87"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="890">
		<text>Come on guys..you really trink this is better than fight club, Forest gump, Matrix or lotr?! It is not!!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="365">
		<text>Sometimes the dream is reality, and the reality may be a dream.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="376">
		<text>In any case, for its minor flaws this is a great film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="74">
		<text>One or two visits to the hospital, though, will be enough to change most folks' minds.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1038">
		<text>This is what mythic adventures should be.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="425">
		<text>Recommend to Nolan fans.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1011">
		<text>This film is the definition of epic.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="653">
		<text>Watched first day first show after releasing this movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="527">
		<text>I have never left a review for any title, good or bad but this is such a piece of garbage that I registered an IMDB account just to vent my opinion.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="833">
		<text>Very annoying to watch.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="980">
		<text>I have to say I don't usually enjoy watching movies with only subtitles, but this one was so interesting I couldn't stop watching it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="255">
		<text>but really what a movie hats off to the LOTR team.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="751">
		<text>Acting and plot is excellent.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Acting" polarity="positive" from="0" to="6"/>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="positive" from="11" to="15"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="637">
		<text>I guess most people take the Lord of the Rings trilogy very serious.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="683">
		<text>The action and special effects were great, but those are tiny upsides in comparision.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="positive" from="4" to="10"/>
			<aspectTerm term="special effects" polarity="positive" from="15" to="30"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="451">
		<text>Open your mind sit back and enjoy a good movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="185">
		<text>Yeah its a good movie I guess, not the greatest of all time in my book but still vastly enjoyable by movie fans of all sorts, even fans of other types of movies</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="250">
		<text>I have never seen a better film adaptation of a book.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="book" polarity="neutral" from="48" to="52"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="316">
		<text>So i watched this film maybe 10 times Russian version, 5 original English.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="189">
		<text>I still say it sucks,sucks,sucks,sucks,sucks,sucks,sucks.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="164">
		<text>Every scene is so memorable, that I just can't think of any reason to rate this movie lower than a 10/10.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="scene" polarity="positive" from="6" to="11"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="509">
		<text>This is an Oscar winning movie</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="730">
		<text>Can't be over, I want more!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1050">
		<text>Well, it was pretty, but the holes in the plot, and the plodding method of exposing intellectual content was dismaying.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="holes in the plot" polarity="negative" from="29" to="46"/>
			<aspectTerm term="plodding method of exposing intellectual content" polarity="negative" from="56" to="104"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="283">
		<text>Battle scenes gave me motion sickness.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Battle scenes" polarity="negative" from="0" to="13"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="950">
		<text>Phenomenal film from top to bottom.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="342">
		<text>Avoid at all cost, this movie is boring !</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1024">
		<text>kind of a braveheart type story but you felt more for william wallace than you did maximus.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="148">
		<text>Should have shot some good day light scenes.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="128">
		<text>I'm convinced this is the movie that drove heath ledger insane</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="690">
		<text>Battle scenes make 90% of the movie. More than enough to walk out.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Battle scenes" polarity="negative" from="0" to="13"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="542">
		<text>This movie is everything that's wrong with Hollywood.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="860">
		<text>Lotsa flashing lights and loud noises, little else.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1089">
		<text>It's not bad but it's not that good.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="718">
		<text>First Time i saw the movie in 3D. It was a great experience for me.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="experience" polarity="positive" from="49" to="59"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="903">
		<text>It did have nice special effects though.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="special effects" polarity="positive" from="17" to="32"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="67">
		<text>City of Angels wasn't even this weird.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="591">
		<text>The special effects were good, but that's about it.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="special effects" polarity="positive" from="4" to="19"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="412">
		<text>Willful suspension of disbelief is one thing, but insulting the intelligence of a 5 year old is another.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1030">
		<text>Although I don't love this kind of epic movies, I have to agree that it's not bad to see people sacrifice for the man and the man finally recalls his wife and children.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="320">
		<text>I give the film 10 stars</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="515">
		<text>JOKER is a gift to the audiences.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="463">
		<text>I'm writing it after seeing this movie for the third time and I feel that I'm ready to say that this it the best sci-fi movie of all time.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="315">
		<text>I highly recommend you see this movie!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1143">
		<text>I was deeply attracted by the ups and downs of the story in the movie.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="ups and downs of the story" polarity="positive" from="30" to="56"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="113">
		<text>The critics that didn't give this movie a near perfect score are on crack.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="critics" polarity="negative" from="4" to="11"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1081">
		<text>I thought character development was great and pacing.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="character development" polarity="positive" from="10" to="31"/>
			<aspectTerm term="pacing" polarity="positive" from="46" to="52"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="695">
		<text>Let's face it, the movie has it's qualities. But by no means beautiful scenery, goodlooking special effects and good direction mean a good movie.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="scenery" polarity="positive" from="71" to="78"/>
			<aspectTerm term="special effects" polarity="positive" from="92" to="107"/>
			<aspectTerm term="direction" polarity="positive" from="117" to="126"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="392">
		<text>Lost in the sauce.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="440">
		<text>So many feelings throughout this movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1097">
		<text>The start was cool but turned out to be a more comedy movie instead of a drama.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="start" polarity="positive" from="4" to="9"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="420">
		<text>It's a film that leads you to think about yourself and your plans in your life.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="484">
		<text>The acting,music and cinematography are just amazing !</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="4" to="10"/>
			<aspectTerm term="music" polarity="positive" from="11" to="16"/>
			<aspectTerm term="cinematography" polarity="positive" from="21" to="35"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="644">
		<text>And this time (compare to the first), it has more typical boring love story ingredient.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="love story ingredient" polarity="negative" from="65" to="86"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="35">
		<text>If you have free time and no problem with open and stupid violence for the sace of violence, this movie is deffenetly for you.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="violence" polarity="negative" from="58" to="66"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="911">
		<text>No history, too many heroes, and nothing with sense.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="history" polarity="negative" from="3" to="10"/>
			<aspectTerm term="heroes" polarity="negative" from="21" to="27"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="881">
		<text>Made the bad or evil cast dominating from start to finish.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="840">
		<text>The dialogue is jarring.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="dialogue" polarity="negative" from="4" to="12"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="837">
		<text>Poor casting.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="casting" polarity="negative" from="5" to="12"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="666">
		<text>The last scenes were so beautiful.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="last scenes" polarity="positive" from="4" to="15"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="158">
		<text>This movie translates from the book perfectly!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="translates from the book" polarity="positive" from="11" to="35"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="380">
		<text>This is a spectacular film, beautifully shot.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="shot" polarity="positive" from="40" to="44"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="565">
		<text>Vastly overrated.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="940">
		<text>a flawless dark masterpiece.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="549">
		<text>Hated was looking forward to it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="493">
		<text>Like some politicians, they feel so frustrated when people from the lower class does not accept their funding champions.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="politicians" polarity="negative" from="10" to="21"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="705">
		<text>Watched crying and over and over!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="806">
		<text>I like the bit where she hits herself in the face with a hammer</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="the bit where she hits herself in the face with a hammer" polarity="positive" from="7" to="63"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="192">
		<text>Nothing more than gangster movie at all.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="300">
		<text>I would (and do) recommend this film to anyone and everyone.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="897">
		<text>Why does everyone think this movie is so good.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="953">
		<text>Well worth the watch.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1162">
		<text>A great film full of funny moments with quirky and the most creative characters that I can say I have known, and also some seriousness and mystery to mix together to make a astonishing film that is practically flawles</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="moments" polarity="positive" from="27" to="34"/>
			<aspectTerm term="characters" polarity="positive" from="69" to="79"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="161">
		<text>To think that Puza wrote this specifically to make a hit is at first crazy.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="5">
		<text>A vivid, unpredictable and movie on man-bonding, class warfare, consumer-driven society and mental disorders.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="947">
		<text>Over all great movie ending.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="positive" from="21" to="27"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="831">
		<text>The basis of the story is great, I was enjoying the events and everything was going well, but then it turned into illogical movie.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="basis of the story" polarity="positive" from="4" to="22"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="152">
		<text>The Godfather is arguably the best gangster drama as well as setting the standard for cinema.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="104">
		<text>Perfectly written and perfectly performed with 3 of the best acting performances you will see from Bale, Eckhart and Ledger.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="written" polarity="positive" from="10" to="17"/>
			<aspectTerm term="performed" polarity="positive" from="32" to="41"/>
			<aspectTerm term="acting performances" polarity="positive" from="61" to="80"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Bale" polarity="positive" from="99" to="103"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Eckhart" polarity="positive" from="105" to="112"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Ledger" polarity="positive" from="117" to="123"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="700">
		<text>This and infinity war are on totally different levels to any other super hero film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="296">
		<text>Don't want to say any words about this film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="393">
		<text>idea was good but the movie is too irritating, boring and way too long</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="idea" polarity="positive" from="0" to="4"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="175">
		<text>I will never forget &quot;The Godfather&quot;.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="415">
		<text>Since i had't much sleep in the last few days. I saw this movie for what it actually is.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="19">
		<text>Edward Norten and Brad Pitt movies are great. They are two great actors watch their movies, except for Keeping the Faith (wasn't great).</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Edward Norten" polarity="positive" from="0" to="13"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Brad Pitt" polarity="positive" from="18" to="27"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="864">
		<text>It was boring and I Sleep when I watch the movie It was Kid Family friendly I don't get any jokes the best thing in this movie is Thanos Poor CGI</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="jokes" polarity="negative" from="92" to="97"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Thanos" polarity="positive" from="130" to="136"/>
			<aspectTerm term="CGI" polarity="negative" from="142" to="145"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="696">
		<text>Movies should entertain! This one certainly doesn't!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="135">
		<text>This is too violent.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="894">
		<text>If you have an invincible monster exactly what can happen in the end.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="672">
		<text>It has Gollum which is pretty good .</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Gollum" polarity="positive" from="7" to="13"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="652">
		<text>What a great movie it was.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="655">
		<text>This movie shows CGI in full effects.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="CGI" polarity="positive" from="17" to="20"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="916">
		<text>Theme was incomprehensible.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Theme" polarity="negative" from="0" to="5"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="926">
		<text>Even the language is in brazilian.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="brazilian" polarity="neutral" from="24" to="33"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="609">
		<text>Still in 2019 a lot of people will this this movie as science fiction, I could watch it over and over and still discover need things and details that can relate to real life event.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="319">
		<text>When i have watched this film first time, after started to follow the career of the actor Morgan Freeman.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Morgan Freeman" polarity="neutral" from="90" to="104"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="741">
		<text>This movie is filled with emotions.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="356">
		<text>It is just so boring and everytime I turn on TNN or something it is on!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="389">
		<text>Why are we supposed to care about the fate of this man and his shallow mission?</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="mission" polarity="negative" from="71" to="78"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="130">
		<text>Serves well for comic fanboys but what about a layman?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="503">
		<text>Please go watch this movie!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="257">
		<text>only one thing i don't like that movie is very lengthy otherwise its a masterpiece.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="473">
		<text>Don't waste your time with this!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="116">
		<text>One of the greats!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="71">
		<text>Gratuitous violence and a cheesy made-for-teenagers twist at the end.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="violence" polarity="negative" from="11" to="19"/>
			<aspectTerm term="twist at the end" polarity="negative" from="52" to="68"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="727">
		<text>Thanx Marvel for doing such art and make it exists.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Marvel" polarity="positive" from="6" to="12"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="246">
		<text>Loved the story, battle scenes and set design.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="10" to="15"/>
			<aspectTerm term="battle scenes" polarity="positive" from="17" to="30"/>
			<aspectTerm term="set design" polarity="positive" from="35" to="45"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="877">
		<text>I left about half way through the movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="304">
		<text>I first read the book, and I didn't liked it that much, but then I saw the movie.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="book" polarity="negative" from="17" to="21"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1113">
		<text>the ending is unexpected and cool. it give me different view on the struggle that rich and poor people face in this world.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="positive" from="4" to="10"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="659">
		<text>The helms deep battle seemed to go on and on and on</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="The helms deep battle" polarity="neutral" from="0" to="21"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="222">
		<text>The movie is too long and almost put me asleep. Even though,great acting by Al.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="66" to="72"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="39">
		<text>I rented this and started watching it and stopped about an hour in intending to go back and finish it the next day.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="286">
		<text>Overdone computer graphics.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="computer graphics" polarity="negative" from="9" to="26"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="446">
		<text>The best movies make you feel something.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="419">
		<text>After watching this insane movie in the theatres back in 2014 I swore to god I will wait 5 years to watch it again so I get to forget it and experince the insanity it has again This without doubt is THE BEST MOVIE EVER MADE</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="59">
		<text>Took me 2 hours to finally drift into an uneasy sleep.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="261">
		<text>Extremely boring and long movie with poor storyline.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="storyline" polarity="negative" from="42" to="51"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="856">
		<text>Do not waist your time on this one, please</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="861">
		<text>Went home and watched &quot;The Wolverine&quot; (the second one) to be reminded of what I like in a popcorn flick.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="981">
		<text>It was like a roller coaster of emotions.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1034">
		<text>To me, this is an inspiring movie, a tale of a man fallen in disgrace because of others , that managed to redeem himself in history once again.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="381">
		<text>The storyline is intense, there's a LOT of timeline jumps (which normally annoy the hell out of me), so you'll have to pay attention.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="storyline" polarity="positive" from="4" to="13"/>
			<aspectTerm term="timeline jumps" polarity="neutral" from="43" to="57"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="878">
		<text>Lots of stabbing and banging sounds.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="sounds" polarity="neutral" from="29" to="35"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1151">
		<text>You have absolutely astonishing animation and color.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="animation" polarity="positive" from="32" to="41"/>
			<aspectTerm term="color" polarity="positive" from="46" to="51"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="167">
		<text>This is one of the best movies i have ever seen,the way they directed it was really good and actors have performed very well in their own characters</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="directed" polarity="positive" from="61" to="69"/>
			<aspectTerm term="actors" polarity="positive" from="93" to="99"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="89">
		<text>What is that for god sake The worst ever and ever</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="14">
		<text>I was very pleased with the entire film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1015">
		<text>Ridley Scott always get his best in visual aura of the movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1007">
		<text>Battle scenes too fast-paced with jerky camera--thought I was watching war movies while on acid!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Battle scenes" polarity="negative" from="0" to="13"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="205">
		<text>Watch the horse's head scene and see how badly edited it is.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="edited" polarity="negative" from="47" to="53"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1014">
		<text>One of my all time favorite Ridley Scott movies, keeps you entertained all the way through and spectacular movie making at its best</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="making" polarity="positive" from="113" to="119"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="626">
		<text>One of the strengths of &quot;Fellowship&quot; was that it while it stayed true to the spirit of the book, it made some very smart choices about which scenes to delete or change, which translated into a better movie. &quot;Two Towers&quot; fails to live up to its predecessor in this respect.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Fellowship" polarity="positive" from="25" to="35"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="162">
		<text>This movie is simply perfect.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="184">
		<text>Mr. Brando and Al Pacino both make this long film bearable.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Mr. Brando" polarity="positive" from="0" to="10"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Al Pacino" polarity="positive" from="15" to="24"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="279">
		<text>I hate when peoples don`t ever use advisors (e.g. Battle Orders) All the moneys gone to FX. And no one cares if battles looks just stupid...</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Battle Orders" polarity="negative" from="50" to="63"/>
			<aspectTerm term="FX" polarity="neutral" from="88" to="90"/>
			<aspectTerm term="battles" polarity="negative" from="112" to="119"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="28">
		<text>Yes, this is one of the finest acting pieces.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting pieces" polarity="positive" from="31" to="44"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="360">
		<text>Although it might relly to much on exposition, &quot;Inception&quot; is a mind blowing film with amazing visuals and action scenes and a fascinating script.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Inception" polarity="positive" from="48" to="57"/>
			<aspectTerm term="visuals" polarity="positive" from="95" to="102"/>
			<aspectTerm term="action scenes" polarity="positive" from="107" to="120"/>
			<aspectTerm term="script" polarity="positive" from="139" to="145"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="807">
		<text>Awesomely directed and played to a good detail.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="directed" polarity="positive" from="10" to="18"/>
			<aspectTerm term="played" polarity="positive" from="23" to="29"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1142">
		<text>Hayao Miyazaki is indeed the most famous animated film master of modern times!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Hayao Miyazaki" polarity="positive" from="0" to="14"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="684">
		<text>A movie about walking? What a waste of time!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1124">
		<text>This is the third so-called masterpiece of the genre that I have seen, and I simply don't get it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="805">
		<text>But none the less a good murder/mystery and lots of drama.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="204">
		<text>It's one of those must see movies but its just over rated.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="259">
		<text>The liberties taken with the story were almost forgivable in the previous two movies, but The Return of the King is just hogwash in my view.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="neutral" from="29" to="34"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="422">
		<text>THIS IS A MANKIND ACHIEVEMENT. THE BEST MOVIE EVER MADE. IS ANYONE HAS DOUBT?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="556">
		<text>Just went and watched the joker movie and it has to be the worst movie I have ever seen 1 out of 5 star</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1116">
		<text>This is so creepy, disturbing, and abnormal, honestly don't know what was going on.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1000">
		<text>Unfortunately, they are still superficial and procedural plots are boring.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="553">
		<text>Not sure what movie the other people were watching.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="777">
		<text>A love story so magically told.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="told" polarity="positive" from="26" to="30"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1134">
		<text>A bucket list film for any movie fanatic.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="429">
		<text>I forced myself to watch it till the end. Soo boooooring.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="57">
		<text>The violence and filming methods made this movie the most disturbing.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="violence" polarity="negative" from="4" to="12"/>
			<aspectTerm term="filming methods" polarity="negative" from="17" to="32"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="699">
		<text>Watch this masterpiece for the love of God!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="145">
		<text>However, Batman stories are corny and tongue-in-cheek.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="624">
		<text>I loved most of this film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1117">
		<text>Good luck redeeming yourself after watching this.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="343">
		<text>I don't understand why this movie is so popular.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="958">
		<text>A fantastic plot and brilliant narrative structure.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="positive" from="12" to="16"/>
			<aspectTerm term="narrative structure" polarity="positive" from="31" to="50"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="529">
		<text>Story was just really unconvincing.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Story" polarity="negative" from="0" to="5"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="270">
		<text>Advertising, advertising, advertising and there is no contents.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="669">
		<text>It will no doubt be a timeless classic that people will watch for generations to come!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="388">
		<text>I could not relate to any character and did not care about the outcome.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="character" polarity="negative" from="26" to="35"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="865">
		<text>I enjoyed all of the Avengers movies, but this one was very disappointed.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="417">
		<text>A multi layered snooze fest and a reminder of how abysmal the DiCaprio's acting really is.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="DiCaprio's acting" polarity="negative" from="62" to="79"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="938">
		<text>Definitely one of the greatest of the greats.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1078">
		<text>I found this film to be an okay film but I don't think it's as good as it's high rating suggests but each to their own and obviously a lot of watchers wouldn't agree with me.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="95">
		<text>It is just what you want for the best movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1029">
		<text>Heroic story set in Roman times with some terrific battle fight scenes, gorgeous set pieces and lovely musical score.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="battle fight scenes" polarity="positive" from="51" to="70"/>
			<aspectTerm term="set" polarity="positive" from="13" to="16"/>
			<aspectTerm term="musical score" polarity="positive" from="103" to="116"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="759">
		<text>If ur not rdy to cry dont watch it rly sad movie got me rly emotional.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="87">
		<text>it might be more landfill material you would enjoy watching.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1144">
		<text>Chihiro is really a kind and brave girl.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1146">
		<text>I really like the animation in Spirited Away. It appears clean and smooth, plus the storyline is very good.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="animation" polarity="positive" from="18" to="27"/>
			<aspectTerm term="storyline" polarity="positive" from="84" to="93"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="710">
		<text>This movie has it all and needs to be watched PERIOD!!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="78">
		<text>The plot twist here is so ridiculous, so embarassingly idiotic, that you suddenly feel ashamed to have enjoyed the film up to the point of its revelation.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot twist" polarity="negative" from="4" to="14"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="767">
		<text>The meaning of this moive to me is let me love more my life, take care more of my life. love my firends around me.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="278">
		<text>is Gandalf actually a wizard? If so, I must have the same powers as him, because I can also point a flashlight at things that fly in the sky!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Gandalf" polarity="neutral" from="3" to="10"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="614">
		<text>If they can recapture 1% of the magic in this film it will be a return to form</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="46">
		<text>It just gets stupid and stupider.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="599">
		<text>Getting lost in another world, is interly what Cinema is made for.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="9">
		<text>Telling the tale of a broken man in a unique way.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="200">
		<text>I would not watch it again.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="156">
		<text>This is truly the peak of filmmaking.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="filmmaking" polarity="positive" from="26" to="36"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="600">
		<text>This one takes you into a whole new universe interly .</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="922">
		<text>This is one of the most beatiful movie ever.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1095">
		<text>Very violent for no reason, there are loads of other movies put there saying the same story in a much better way.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="966">
		<text>This film is one of my absolute favorites.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="179">
		<text>Great scenario, perfect fiction, very good acting.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="scenario" polarity="positive" from="6" to="14"/>
			<aspectTerm term="fiction" polarity="positive" from="24" to="31"/>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="43" to="49"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="399">
		<text>This movie should have been right up my street.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="983">
		<text>Good, but wish it to be better in deal of story, like taxi driver, makes me remember it so much</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="606">
		<text>When we will see another movie with the same speed? So deeply philosophical? Sadly, the most likely answer is. NEVER</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="291">
		<text>Were they serving some drugged cool-aid that I missed?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="508">
		<text>Best acting and story.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="5" to="11"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="16" to="21"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1070">
		<text>Started interesting but mid-way through it became boring and not compelling.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="636">
		<text>The trees were cool and so was Gollum.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="trees" polarity="positive" from="4" to="9"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Gollum" polarity="positive" from="31" to="37"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="390">
		<text>It is not like he was doing anything important or life changing.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="210">
		<text>The story is hard to follow and lost me several times along the way.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="814">
		<text>Excellent movie by one of my favorite directors.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="102">
		<text>Dark, mature, sophisticated, exhilarating, emotional, and a true acting powerhouse.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="65" to="71"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="243">
		<text>It is action packed, fantasy filled and thoroughly exciting.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="neutral" from="6" to="12"/>
			<aspectTerm term="fantasy" polarity="neutral" from="21" to="28"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="123">
		<text>I can't believe how many people think it's a great movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="101">
		<text>Nothing before or since has even came close (including the other two movies in this trilogy) and probably never will.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="560">
		<text>Had it been made and released today it would receive a fraction of its hype or praise.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="748">
		<text>It is a fine love story with a sad ending because life is not always happy.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="love story" polarity="positive" from="13" to="23"/>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="neutral" from="35" to="41"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1123">
		<text>I am not an anime fan.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="428">
		<text>The plot is completly has no logic and its not intersting at all.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="4" to="8"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="541">
		<text>Save your money and re-watch Heath ledger's joker.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Heath ledger's joker" polarity="neutral" from="29" to="49"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="952">
		<text>And it sticks close to the actual events.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="187">
		<text>There aren't many movies that are so bad I don't watch the whole thing, but &quot;The Godfather&quot; is that bad.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="290">
		<text>Was there some weird subliminal suggestion that I'm immune to?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="948">
		<text>10 star rating for me.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="230">
		<text>We watched Frodo and the others live like two separate films.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="842">
		<text>Even the editing is inconsistent.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="editing" polarity="negative" from="9" to="16"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="828">
		<text>Acting is okay, story though, ugh, what a poor attempt.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Acting" polarity="neutral" from="0" to="6"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="negative" from="16" to="21"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="887">
		<text>A special effects movie with no plot.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="32" to="36"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="100">
		<text>Quite obviously the best superhero movie ever made.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="242">
		<text>It will no doubt be a timeless classic that people will watch for generations to come!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="10">
		<text>Diving deep into the shattered psyche of the main character the audience is presented a tale of love, loss, and showing how the mind copes.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="585">
		<text>Nearly mindless Hollywood action/kung-fu/sci-fi entertainment.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="410">
		<text>I cannot see the appeal in this movie, its Nolan's worst in my opinion, but i'm sure you'll love it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1090">
		<text>The film was ok, I think a LOT of people tried to read into it too much and find way too much symbolism.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="747">
		<text>Bring your tissues. This movie is sad but also beautiful at the same time.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="178">
		<text>the acting level is incomparable.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting level" polarity="positive" from="4" to="16"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="858">
		<text>Feel like watching stupid drama series.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="361">
		<text>Inception surely is a stunning view, an amazing and visual thrilling experience, but it came with a price.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="experience" polarity="positive" from="69" to="79"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="321">
		<text>This film will go down in history as one of the greats!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="297">
		<text>It is well constructed, the acting is superb and the characters are so likeable or in the case of the pigs so detestable.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="28" to="34"/>
			<aspectTerm term="characters" polarity="positive" from="53" to="63"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="7">
		<text>Since it is an adaptation from a book, it perfectly meets the expectations with nuances and twists.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="nuances" polarity="positive" from="80" to="87"/>
			<aspectTerm term="twists" polarity="positive" from="92" to="98"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="847">
		<text>Don't waste your time watching it like I did.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="520">
		<text>I don't understand why people liked this movie so much.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1102">
		<text>I expected this to much better than snowpiercer.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="239">
		<text>One of the best movies of the series, I like the massive battle at the end of the movie.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="series" polarity="neutral" from="30" to="36"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1020">
		<text>I'd replace some of those scenes with a really good chariot race!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="504">
		<text>This is the first time I've ever wrote a review on this app and I've been using it to read reviews for years! That's how good this film is.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="752">
		<text>I can't help being crying after watching this.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="812">
		<text>Believe me, he's made it here - this is a film that revels in its audience's discomfort.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="21">
		<text>Be prepared for an awesome twist, and read the book based on it.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="twist" polarity="positive" from="27" to="32"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1152">
		<text>A great relatable main character as it showcases her flawless character development with leadership, determination, and hope.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="main character" polarity="positive" from="18" to="32"/>
			<aspectTerm term="character development" polarity="positive" from="62" to="83"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="846">
		<text>Cannot think why this movie has so many favourable reviews.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1133">
		<text>Bizarre yet appropriate, this film did a fantastic job at presenting other culture and the storys that come with.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="job at presenting other culture" polarity="positive" from="51" to="82"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1150">
		<text>Unique story that makes sure people will love it.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="7" to="12"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="70">
		<text>helena bone ham carter was good as bellatrix lestrange.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="helena bone ham carter" polarity="positive" from="0" to="22"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1032">
		<text>In the endless sound of the end music, my mood is also like the gladiator of the last moment of victory.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="886">
		<text>Not one likeable character.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="character" polarity="negative" from="17" to="26"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="525">
		<text>they can't do people like this.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="546">
		<text>lets get the virtue signalling started now</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1068">
		<text>There are way too many movies which are much much better.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1148">
		<text>The starting of the movie is very nice but in second half its not as good as the starting because the final act occurs too fast due to which the ending does'nt looks so good.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="starting" polarity="positive" from="4" to="12"/>
			<aspectTerm term="second half" polarity="negative" from="46" to="57"/>
			<aspectTerm term="starting" polarity="positive" from="81" to="89"/>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="negative" from="145" to="151"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="995">
		<text>Don't have a word to describe how good this movie is.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="172">
		<text>I did get a little bored here and there. But this film is classic.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="202">
		<text>Seem pretty boring for me want my type, plus its an old movie</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="90">
		<text>Sorry but I thought this movie was so hyped up for nothing.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1046">
		<text>He fighted many times with the revenge against a ling of Rome under his mind.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="924">
		<text>The story of the movie is connected with each part of the movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="883">
		<text>I can't believe all the overhype this movie sucks Zero plot .</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="55" to="59"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="514">
		<text>Amazing directing by Todd Phillips &amp; amazing cinematography by Lawrence Sher.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="directing" polarity="positive" from="8" to="17"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Todd Phillips" polarity="neutral" from="21" to="34"/>
			<aspectTerm term="cinematography" polarity="positive" from="45" to="59"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Lawrence Sher" polarity="neutral" from="63" to="76"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="875">
		<text>It was simply waste of time and money.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1149">
		<text>Many consider this to be Hayao Miyazaki's masterpiece.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="656">
		<text>The battle of Helm's Deep like a live action on CGI which works so perfectly.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="battle of Helm's Deep" polarity="positive" from="4" to="25"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="544">
		<text>The luvvies, the shallow and the right on brigade will love it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="264">
		<text>The action and special effects were great tho.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="positive" from="4" to="10"/>
			<aspectTerm term="special effects" polarity="positive" from="15" to="30"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="601">
		<text>The first time i watched this, i was absolutely amazed with the concept of it.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="concept" polarity="positive" from="64" to="71"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="662">
		<text>The Fellowship was better than I had expected and gave the impression of an even better sequense.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="The Fellowship" polarity="positive" from="0" to="14"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="647">
		<text>And guess what, I'm going to watch the final chapter of this trilogy, too!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1008">
		<text>Spartacus on A&amp;E Biography was much more interesting and entertaining.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="424">
		<text>Not Nolan's greatest work, Interstellar is a slow burn mind bender but it keeps you in the game until the end, and features stunning visuals and a great cast.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="visuals" polarity="positive" from="133" to="140"/>
			<aspectTerm term="cast" polarity="positive" from="153" to="157"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="168">
		<text>This is the type of movie you just want to watch time and time again.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="816">
		<text>anyone who hasn't watched this yet I highly recommend it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="408">
		<text>I watched this twice, once alone and once with some family.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="761">
		<text>Have read the book and didn't mind watching it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="649">
		<text>It was just not that good, but it's watchable and well done.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="289">
		<text>It is probably the worst movie that I have ever seen. Its only rivals are the two previous LOR movies.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="LOR" polarity="negative" from="91" to="94"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="850">
		<text>I'm so annoyed I came here just to write this review.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="326">
		<text>I really can't explain why this movie does absolutely nothing for me.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="707">
		<text>It is a beautiful film and worth watching and has a special artistic touch I swear.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="artistic" polarity="positive" from="60" to="68"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="335">
		<text>Shawshank is nothing more than a fairy tale.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="208">
		<text>Coppola should be ashamed.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Coppola" polarity="negative" from="0" to="7"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="692">
		<text>Why does everyone think this movie is some kind of masterpiece which is set to redefine cinema?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1044">
		<text>Do they read History in hollywood?</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="421">
		<text>I am a real series/movies' lover and. This was awesome.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="744">
		<text>Acting, story, music, screenplay everything is beautiful and a treat to watch.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Acting" polarity="positive" from="0" to="6"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="8" to="13"/>
			<aspectTerm term="music" polarity="positive" from="15" to="20"/>
			<aspectTerm term="screenplay" polarity="positive" from="22" to="32"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="121">
		<text>His joker is iconic truly a bar to reach for, for all other actors.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="joker" polarity="positive" from="4" to="9"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="566">
		<text>Overly complex, much of which is just for the writer/directors to show how clever they are.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="414">
		<text>High reviews had their 10 rating planted into their head that this was actually a good movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="371">
		<text>Got so deep i don't think even the writers know wtf is going on any more at the end there</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="207">
		<text>Wobbly sound and out of focus cuts throughout.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="sound" polarity="negative" from="7" to="12"/>
			<aspectTerm term="cuts" polarity="negative" from="30" to="34"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="826">
		<text>Garbage movie - plot wise.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="16" to="20"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="58">
		<text>I enjoy a good violent film every now and then, but this movie left me with a bad taste in my mouth and a sick feeling in my stomach.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="584">
		<text>I give it a 6.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1009">
		<text>I love the music for this for then the actual film it got slow and dull at many points for me but I would still watch it again.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="music" polarity="positive" from="11" to="16"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="677">
		<text>Well.in my opinion.Greed is often the beginning of destruction</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="635">
		<text>I know it was in the book... but made for quite a boring time.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="680">
		<text>What's boring about part 2? Simply everything!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1119">
		<text>I don't even know who can vote this more than 3 stars</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="345">
		<text>The acting was good, and the plot original, but it was still a rather ordinary movie.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="4" to="10"/>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="neutral" from="29" to="33"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1114">
		<text>I know that some people are really into this but I just didn't get it unfortunately</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="867">
		<text>Disney ruined more great characters by having too political writers involved and ruining important characterizations of developed and loved personas.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Disney" polarity="negative" from="0" to="6"/>
			<aspectTerm term="writers" polarity="negative" from="60" to="67"/>
			<aspectTerm term="characterizations" polarity="negative" from="99" to="116"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="225">
		<text>I thought this was a very good movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="764">
		<text>You can't miss falling in love with them.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1069">
		<text>Don't get all the fuss about this film, it is very average in every possible way.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1096">
		<text>Movie is excellent till 1st half but in 2nd half you get bored irritating and may be scratch your hair</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="1st half" polarity="positive" from="24" to="32"/>
			<aspectTerm term="2nd half" polarity="negative" from="40" to="48"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="845">
		<text>Those cops must be the dumbest on the planet missing so many clues !</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="539">
		<text>For once I actually agree with the actual critics who graded this film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="976">
		<text>A great show of rise to power and downfalls.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="show of rise to power and downfalls" polarity="positive" from="8" to="43"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="317">
		<text>Read both book versions.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="book" polarity="neutral" from="10" to="14"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1099">
		<text>The film is highly unrealistic and beyond surprises.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1093">
		<text>5 stars for the exceptional acting though</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="28" to="34"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="524">
		<text>I went to the pay counter to ask my money back for the 2 hours of torture.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="53">
		<text>It's only mildly amusing before the fighting if you're a mentally stable person.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="811">
		<text>David Fincher claims he's always wanted to make a date movie that made three million people get divorces as a result.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="784">
		<text>It really a a awesome movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1135">
		<text>Before to watch it, make you ready to see the all unconscious symbols of Miyazaki!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="483">
		<text>Enjoy this masterpiece because Joaquin Phoenix and Todd Phillips overdid themselves with this movie .</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Joaquin Phoenix" polarity="positive" from="31" to="46"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Todd Phillips" polarity="positive" from="51" to="64"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="853">
		<text>I would not waste my time watching the movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="502">
		<text>The movie was excellent and amazing, from the beginning that Joaquin's personality is seen as he evolves in the Joker until the end, Joker is the most difficult character to do and I think Joaquin did it!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Joker" polarity="neutral" from="112" to="117"/>
			<aspectTerm term="Joaquin" polarity="positive" from="61" to="68"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="469">
		<text>I also didn't think it had an ending. It kind of stopped.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="negative" from="30" to="36"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1110">
		<text>And beacose it takes 2 hours you must have a lot of patience</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1049">
		<text>Watching such a film with legendary heroism in such an era is especially awe-inspiring and precious.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1002">
		<text>Gladiator is a great film, not only for it's gore, but for it's performances.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="gore" polarity="positive" from="45" to="49"/>
			<aspectTerm term="performances" polarity="positive" from="64" to="76"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="41">
		<text>I would give Edward Norton an oscar for this movie and still rate it at &quot;6&quot; because crazy people are not worth so much of my time and energy.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Edward Norton" polarity="positive" from="13" to="26"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1056">
		<text>I watched this movie. it's a good movie but i couldn't understand how it won the best picture.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="406">
		<text>So basically why would you leave the ending like this, like mans here thinking omg the spinning thing is gonna drop because it's wobbling and then you have the audacity to cut the damn sceen WHAT DO YOU MEAN BROOO</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="negative" from="37" to="43"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="895">
		<text>Two rules of storytelling: (1) heroes always win, and (2) if you have to explain it, you didn't tell it well enough.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="643">
		<text>It can be a good rental so you can watch it at home and complete many household chores at the same time.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="328">
		<text>I get a similar vibe from FORREST GUMP and TERMS OF ENDEARMENT, to name a couple others.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="73">
		<text>The drivel disguised as philosophy will fool the naive and someone, somewhere will be dumb enough to emulate the fighting.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="945">
		<text>This movie presented the dangerous gangster rise and fall.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="721">
		<text>ALL RECOMMENDATION if you're fan of superheros</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="25">
		<text>Don't get me wrong. Fight Club is entertaining.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1139">
		<text>the story told us a lot. love is forever</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="neutral" from="4" to="9"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="403">
		<text>The music and effects were great.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="music" polarity="positive" from="4" to="9"/>
			<aspectTerm term="effects" polarity="positive" from="14" to="21"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="804">
		<text>This is a great movie even though I think the ending was odd in my view.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="ending" polarity="negative" from="46" to="52"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="217">
		<text>I didn't like it and I guess I should have known I wouldn't. Cheers to those who do.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="134">
		<text>Waste of great actors.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="648">
		<text>It is to be hoped that I won't fall asleep.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="640">
		<text>There is a lot of walking around and talking in The Two Towers, and it's tough for a three hour movie to still be compelling.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="walking around" polarity="neutral" from="18" to="32"/>
			<aspectTerm term="talking" polarity="neutral" from="37" to="44"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1033">
		<text>The whole Colosseum is silent and stays in solemn silence for a long time .</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="33">
		<text>The talking is too much.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="talking" polarity="negative" from="4" to="11"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="835">
		<text>Awful claptrap couple of hours of my life lost, never to be reclaimed</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="658">
		<text>This movie is a solid second in the trilogy.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="868">
		<text>WTG Disney for screwing up another movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="957">
		<text>This movie Somehow tops menace to society.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="829">
		<text>Can't believe the same person directed Seven, Fight Club.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="912">
		<text>Marvel has no writers</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Marvel" polarity="negative" from="0" to="6"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="125">
		<text>Bales voice is hilarious.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Bales voice" polarity="positive" from="0" to="11"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="547">
		<text>DO NOT go and waste your money there.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1156">
		<text>A fantastic animated movie like-able characters fun to watch :)</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="animated" polarity="positive" from="12" to="20"/>
			<aspectTerm term="characters" polarity="positive" from="37" to="47"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="117">
		<text>The acting is unparalleled all round.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting" polarity="positive" from="4" to="10"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="311">
		<text>One of the epic and remembered movie of all the time.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="482">
		<text>I get why some people hate this . It's because of the political message and how some people think that you need get empathy for Arthur's madness. But come on that is not the point and it will never be.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="political message" polarity="neutral" from="54" to="71"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="472">
		<text>The screenplay is so bad, I don't know how this movie can have such a big score on iMDb.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="screenplay" polarity="negative" from="4" to="14"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="755">
		<text>BEAUTIFUL EMOTIONAL FILM. LOVED EVERY BIT. MESSAGE IS CLEAR. LIVE IN THE MOMENT AND ENJOY YOUR LIFE DOING WHAT YOU LOVE UNTIL YOU CAN.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="435">
		<text>movie concept is best.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="concept" polarity="positive" from="6" to="13"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="448">
		<text>It made me feel love, hate, hope, sadness, all at the same time.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="16">
		<text>Congrats to all involved in this film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="458">
		<text>I &amp; my wife watched this saga on big screen in Indore, central India &amp; we were mesmerised.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="671">
		<text>Just as good as the first movie, nothing very special about it, could never give it 10 out of 10 although it's a really good movie I doubt I will ever watch it again.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="first" polarity="neutral" from="20" to="25"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="79">
		<text>What were they thinking? The plot is probably written by a three year old kid.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="29" to="33"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="766">
		<text>This has made me cry always regardless of the time I have watched this film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="675">
		<text>Throughout, Sam had accompanied frodo baggins either as a servant or as a friend.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="391">
		<text>Over rated and like some have said style of substance</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="294">
		<text>The Shawshank Redemption has great performances, extremely well written script and story all leading to a deeply emotional climax!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="performances" polarity="positive" from="35" to="47"/>
			<aspectTerm term="script" polarity="positive" from="72" to="78"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="83" to="88"/>
			<aspectTerm term="climax" polarity="positive" from="123" to="129"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="533">
		<text>Just got out of the movie. My humor was much better before seeing it.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1136">
		<text>There was so much massage to our reality world.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="960">
		<text>If you want to calibrate your film maker compass to a status quo let this movie be your instrument.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="569">
		<text>The film has great special effects and fight sequences, but with characters you don't really care about.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="special effects" polarity="positive" from="19" to="34"/>
			<aspectTerm term="fight sequences" polarity="positive" from="39" to="54"/>
			<aspectTerm term="characters" polarity="negative" from="65" to="75"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="285">
		<text>No plot.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="3" to="7"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="882">
		<text>I vote for nonsense movie of the millennium!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="538">
		<text>Way too many 10's!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="299">
		<text>It is the only movie I've seen that has made tears of happiness come to my eyes.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="736">
		<text>If you are even a remote fan of this universe you must watch this!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="353">
		<text>Plz I request all to rate 1 🌟 to movie so others don't waste their time by influence by wrong rating.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="348">
		<text>Thank you Tim Robbins, you are the only reason I could sit through this long winded tale of garbage.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Tim Robbins" polarity="positive" from="10" to="21"/>
			<aspectTerm term="tale" polarity="negative" from="84" to="88"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="769">
		<text>The movie had a lot of parts in it that made me cry, but also very happy scenes.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="374">
		<text>I have watched it a few times and mainly get it, until I find something new I don't get!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="872">
		<text>A lot of good actors in this movie. Use them and quit focusing on CGI!!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="actors" polarity="positive" from="14" to="20"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1066">
		<text>All I wish to say is do not go by the rating or the hype.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="753">
		<text>The movie depicts life's of teens having chronic healt conditions.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="301">
		<text>The characters are so well developped and well interpreted by the actors that you really feel for them which makes the whole story even more compeling.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="characters" polarity="positive" from="4" to="14"/>
			<aspectTerm term="actors" polarity="positive" from="66" to="72"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="125" to="130"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="772">
		<text>Music, emotions, and a beautiful love story.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="love story" polarity="positive" from="33" to="43"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1112">
		<text>didn't care for the excessive violence.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="490">
		<text>The pool does not need the money.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1041">
		<text>Would have been a great film without the end.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="338">
		<text>i do not know how this film can be revered over others such as psycho, apocalypse now, raging bull, easy rider, the godfather, the killing fields, some like it hot and casablanca amongst others.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="781">
		<text>One of the best love shows the feeling of love in emotionally.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="597">
		<text>The film is as well crafted as the matrix itself!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="817">
		<text>Excellent tone, well acted, and has some great twists.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="tone" polarity="positive" from="10" to="14"/>
			<aspectTerm term="acted" polarity="positive" from="21" to="26"/>
			<aspectTerm term="twists" polarity="positive" from="47" to="53"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="103">
		<text>Pure cinema.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="855">
		<text>scored 8.1! Ultimately bad, bad bad.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="793">
		<text>A great adaptation of the book and a really good cast!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="adaptation" polarity="positive" from="8" to="18"/>
			<aspectTerm term="cast" polarity="positive" from="49" to="53"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="918">
		<text>You know you can wrap a a pile of poo in pretty paper and bow but still a pile of poo and thats what this movie is sooooo disapointe</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="665">
		<text>Gollum character was also a good character.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Gollum character" polarity="positive" from="0" to="16"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="137">
		<text>Convoluted story line.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story line" polarity="negative" from="11" to="21"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="470">
		<text>It goes on and on.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="477">
		<text>Breathtaking in summary</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1100">
		<text>I don't know how the Oscar jury works.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="827">
		<text>The plot has more holes than a Swiss cheese.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="4" to="8"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="775">
		<text>Really heart touching cause J really felt the moment!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="91">
		<text>I thought it stinked.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="149">
		<text>Acting was good</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Acting" polarity="positive" from="0" to="6"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="604">
		<text>If you like sci fi action films then this is the film for you.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1120">
		<text>I did not enjoy this the way so many people do.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="537">
		<text>It's not a masterpiece but an ok film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1157">
		<text>A feast of imagination. Stunning visuals. Amazing story line.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="visuals" polarity="positive" from="33" to="40"/>
			<aspectTerm term="story line" polarity="positive" from="50" to="60"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="309">
		<text>Tim Robbins, you make my days a little brighter -- thank you!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Tim Robbins" polarity="positive" from="0" to="11"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="124">
		<text>One of Nolan's worst films.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Nolan" polarity="negative" from="7" to="12"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="571">
		<text>If this is where the movie industry is going, I think we should all be deeply saddened.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="111">
		<text>It is a good combination of good action and awesome storyline.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="positive" from="33" to="39"/>
			<aspectTerm term="storyline" polarity="positive" from="52" to="61"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="232">
		<text>The film in the Shire did not notice anything, and the film added something different.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="29">
		<text>It is sure relates to pop culture of that era the film was made.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="455">
		<text>I was blown away by this film, the sound, the music, the experience!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="sound" polarity="positive" from="35" to="40"/>
			<aspectTerm term="music" polarity="positive" from="46" to="51"/>
			<aspectTerm term="experience" polarity="positive" from="57" to="67"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="879">
		<text>If that is your thing you will like it otherwise a lot of mediocre animated action with little substance.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="action" polarity="negative" from="76" to="82"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="302">
		<text>The structure builts up emotionnaly like only Darabont can do it. Breathtaking!</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Darabont" polarity="positive" from="46" to="54"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="587">
		<text>Go for the matinee cheap seats.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="495">
		<text>One of the best movies in these few years and 100% Oscar worthy Joaquin Phoenix delivers one of the best performances I've ever scene</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Joaquin Phoenix" polarity="positive" from="64" to="79"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1121">
		<text>I do like Chihiro though.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Chihiro" polarity="positive" from="10" to="17"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="480">
		<text>A lot of people will see this movie and think that it encourages violence.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="760">
		<text>I'm 100% sure that I'm going to continue watching this movie over and over again!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="550">
		<text>Its not for anyone to watch.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1103">
		<text>The picture is overrated by critics. Does not contain a story.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="negative" from="56" to="61"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="34">
		<text>It is not told cinematographly it is spoken more.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="578">
		<text>I check my watch several times while in the theater.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="330">
		<text>NO great acting performances(they're OK but not a miracle!)</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="acting performances" polarity="negative" from="9" to="28"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="843">
		<text>The furnishings are more interesting than the actors.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="furnishings" polarity="positive" from="4" to="15"/>
			<aspectTerm term="actors" polarity="negative" from="46" to="52"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="734">
		<text>Forget people who say that this movie is crap,because the way I see it avengers endgame is the most entertaining movie in history so far.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="48">
		<text>Edward Norton attending support groups for problems and diseases he pretended to have. Trying to get Seconal for his insomnia.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="40">
		<text>I thought it was ok.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="906">
		<text>he will win 100% Oscar for the worst scenario and for the worst director</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="scenario" polarity="negative" from="37" to="45"/>
			<aspectTerm term="director" polarity="negative" from="64" to="72"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="900">
		<text>You will be feeling thoroughly cheated while watching this movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="364">
		<text>The director cleverly used some vague clue loopholes to make everyone think that the ending of the movie is open, let people have room for discussion, and smartly let us keep talking after watching, it can be said that it is very smart.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="clue loopholes" polarity="positive" from="38" to="52"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="907">
		<text>Abysmal and embarrassing cinema.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="904">
		<text>Three hours of life I will never get back. Pure crap!</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="552">
		<text>Please pick another movie to go to.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="72">
		<text>I suspect that males under the age of 20 will love it, though.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="915">
		<text>What a terrible film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="203">
		<text>Great Acting dreadful editing.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="Acting" polarity="positive" from="6" to="12"/>
			<aspectTerm term="editing" polarity="negative" from="22" to="29"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="216">
		<text>I tried this film because I thought it would be a good film to see as a student studying film.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="32">
		<text>I was not totally stunned by what I saw.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="929">
		<text>At the beginning I judge this movie will be bored &amp; stupid. Turn out, I give 10/10.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="884">
		<text>Not much to say,it just sucks</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="984">
		<text>Just finished watching this movie and I must say I enjoyed it .</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="971">
		<text>The story is good, but how poverty is romanticized is disgusting.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="story" polarity="positive" from="4" to="9"/>
			<aspectTerm term="how poverty is romanticized" polarity="negative" from="23" to="50"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="453">
		<text>Especially the second half of the movie is really intense of emotions and the final is simply great.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="second half" polarity="positive" from="15" to="26"/>
			<aspectTerm term="final" polarity="positive" from="78" to="83"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1077">
		<text>Parasite (2019) OUCH! Pls make this director stop.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="director" polarity="negative" from="36" to="44"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="195">
		<text>La Piovra - italian tv-series is much better in every point.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="487">
		<text>This movie is a triumph.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="651">
		<text>the final battle scene was epic (about 4 viewings)</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="final battle scene" polarity="positive" from="4" to="22"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="519">
		<text>I thought this movie was complete and utter garbage.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="988">
		<text>The editing flows like a samba.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="editing" polarity="positive" from="4" to="11"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="263">
		<text>It felt like 4 endings put together one after one, I swear he made 4 different endings and put them all in this movie.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="1091">
		<text>It was ok for a movie to watch when you can't find anything else.</text>
	</sentence>
	<sentence id="592">
		<text>The same old plot used over and over again.</text>
		<aspectTerms>
			<aspectTerm term="plot" polarity="negative" from="13" to="17"/>
		</aspectTerms>
	</sentence>
</sentences>
